Come to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
door feel the romance in every arcane lord
people I'm not really concerned about.
What can they do that has not already been done?
It'd be interesting to see their creativity,
but I'm kind of bored with those people.
So whatever.
What can they do?
Obviously, there's three
Obviously, they're pretty sad people
So I'm not gonna go after anybody or harass anybody
They shouldn't probably be going on again as I did sleep all day. Hi
Well, you know, if they're happy, if that makes them happy
I hope they're happy
Because they're fulfilling there they're fulfilling there much purpose, I guess I guess
You know it's sad
I know it's like now it's now it's redundant it's like
please I'd love to see like a good like interesting troll
like a not impressive or not I'm not even a very good troll I'm better than that I'm right
Hey Twinkle, hey Twinkle, I don't think I've met you before but yeah, how about like, you know, I'm like a lover of humanity and then it's like, I just wish people could be more human sometimes.
like the even lower nature than human being is like the monsters, right?
Monsters are just
hurt people probably.
The biggest monsters are like probably there's like some bill inside of them, their inner child.
hurt
If I'm like the catalyst if I'm like the
If I'm the one that they want to go after
Well
Hey, how is the going Jesus Christ?
So I don't know how long I'll be here today
Hey, babe, all right
Yeah, I'm a lucky person
Even if we all know this will be okay like some people like everything you know
It's the one thing that makes me feel good, is you're purring.
Excuse me.
See, even no matter how bad I feel or how bad it is, it's like I got the kitty.
You know, you love me, huh?
If no one else loves me, my cats, right?
Can't argue with that.
Hi there.
You're on purr.
Babe.
Look there, look there.
It wants to be in the mix here as we're talking.
He comes over, you want to be in the mix too?
Here's your star two.
Good cat.
Tricks out all those, all the five cats, he's the one that...
You didn't want all the five cats. Oh, my five cats because I have five cats that he was born a litter of five
And he's one of the five let's see
He's like my little buddy
He kisses
It's just like you know
I hope you have a cat who loves you, who thinks it all better.
I'm going to come up and talk with a nice, friendly person, but you know I have to be
So crazy though, um, they got friends with this guy. His name is Danny stranger. He's like he's had over a million views
Hey, Axe. How are you?
He had over he's had over a million views. He's like he looks like kid rock if he's on right now
You can see what it looks like and stuff
But um, I was on last night, you know, I was having a kind of tough night
And I was on with him and then we're having a good chat and then somebody came on it was somebody familiar
I just don't know who it was. There's a war dog. I don't know
Maybe it was a war dog or something
But he came on and just started
Just started talking all this shit about me and I just lived I just hung up and then
The Danny this kicked him off immediately and he's like come back psyche, but
And thank you for that
It was just one thing after another sometimes.
But that's, but it's funny because it's like he's, it was like, you know, he has a kind of
a smaller show, but it's just like even like on a little small show where like nobody knows me,
you know, except the, the hose, I guess Pyron was on that show before he started it. So,
Small chat like somebody knows me and trying to oh, it's okay, baby. Yeah, but yeah, hopefully we get to talk soon
You have a good night
Yeah, and I want to apologize to ghosts. I feel like I ruined your birthday. I really wish I was in a better mood when I was able to
To do that like fun panel that you wanted to do and stuff
I'm sorry, I slept a lot tonight
like my dream I was at this this restaurant that's right I guess where's where the church used to be
it was a really nice it's a really nice restaurant but it was like the labyrinth and basically
I got lost in it and I was trying to find the way out and it was taking forever and it's like
I just kept passing people I know and stuff and like asking for the way out I even dreamed about
He was like, yeah, I guess he a he I don't know if he's he have a channel
I'm not sure but he was like trying to talk to me this channel and stuff to people and
Pretty weird dream
Eventually like I found my way outside of the restaurant and then I was okay. I'm out and then
All there was was like a huge I started walking up the it was like a big hill up and people walking up the hill
And I couldn't like walk up the like was too steep for me
And I had then I was like climbing and that like the hill turned totally like a mountain side of a mountain as
scrappy on the grass trying to like
Trying to go up and stuff
And I like I couldn't it was like
Then I would like if I like stopped I would fall and so I was just stuck
Yeah
Okay
Yeah, it's
It's just like lately I
Think I've been kind of like more sensitive
Maybe a little bit more sensitive
but
Well, I've always been like sensitive to negativity and it's like and so yeah, and it's like wow. I wish I could be like
Whenever who cares what they say like cares what they say the one. I'm like kind of a more sensitive space
If I'm in right now
it
I'm more effective me and so and I'm sorry if I'm not like in the great mood and I was like, whoa I
Should just stop I should just stop like don't stop going on like just gonna be bad again
Yeah, try three times today
like every time I started getting attacked I just like I just drained
everything out of me and I fell asleep so I don't know yeah hopefully maybe I'll
but
Yeah, I don't want to be a downer though
So if I become too much of a downer if you feel like I'm too much of a turner. I probably will leave again, but it's
it's like, you know, I
Don't want you to think I'm just like
Gonna crawl up and give up like I'm not a quitter
No matter how bad things get
But you know, I there people that rely on me there's people that are like, you know, not maybe
Okay, so I could I can take it like I don't want other people to be
I know there's people that need me, still.
I'll look into unbanning anybody,
but you know, I would say just contact me.
There's on my page, on my web page,
psychyawakens.com, there is a way to send me a message
or you can find me on TikTok, psychyawakens on TikTok.
You can send me a private message for ending me there.
And just explain like what happened or why the version was banned and why they shouldn't be banned
But I keep unbanning people and it's really confusing. There's so many people
so many
So many aliases and stuff gets confusing and I seem to keep unbanning there. I just keep unbanning everybody but
Did a mass on band and so yeah, it could have been Gotti the other day. He was banning people
I think like we took care of most of that
They can have a look
at my thing. I
Can tell everybody who's banned and you can just tell me
They should or should not be
Or at least your opinion about it. I just probably won't do much about it tonight
Okay, so like four days, four or five days ago,
I unbanned everybody.
There was not one person that was banned.
And so then, whoever's banned,
it's new, right?
I'll tell everybody who it is.
Okay, banned users.
Labia Dragher.
Newflayer 368 somebody with a scorpion the scorpion avatar
Joe
Eraser of rain
G hand
Daryl Kostek
Barry's boo Sam clumsy being gang blue room gang Tommy JT
Katie Kip Aiden
Dingle the low key
I think someone said Dingle is Goddy today, right?
Pink, ah, pink Whitney Aiden,
Rodney Dangerfield won't be saved.
Badass MF Aiden, purely phenomenal,
booty bandit, stay turnt 201, West Coast Ryda,
Goddy, Cindy Star, JT, platform boots,
Vader's mom, Todd Wutherford,
why are there so many people?
Wow, this is guys, this is in two days.
This many people in two days smash
Dr. Mad Hatton number one important Billy swallows Radham as prime
Place bow the settlement Westwood stormy seas today
JT allied master computer poopy pants
JT JT and
Jorge arc
Hey, Joe
So if any of those names are familiar and those are people that should not be a
If you're not new Bands, just let me know.
Yeah.
And so that was just yesterday, was it today, Sunday?
Yeah, that was just yesterday and today.
Cause I'm thick on Thursday or Friday, I am banned everybody.
So, no, I can't pull 20 viewers.
Oh, it's 20 viewers, 20 viewers.
So, I miss you wrong.
You should have said 9, you should have said 21 really, really, right?
Again, is it about viewers? It is about like quality, that quantity or quantity or quality is that
I used to have like five viewers and I had a great time
When I started right
And I've had like a hundred viewers and didn't wasn't having such a great time and so would I rather have five
quality people or you know at least like you know five
Genuine people or a hundred assholes
I don't know yeah, obviously
Yeah, and when you're gay you call the sexual deviant your whole life and so yeah
I'm a gay man
Themosexual actually was on the psychological list of like, you know
Mental disorders until like 1970s two or 73, right?
So, but if you still want to use that language some sexual deviant, whatever I
Don't even have sex so it's so funny. I'm such a sexual deviant
Anyway
practically a virgin
So let me see, whatever, I'm gonna have to pin my link.
Anyone wants to come up?
Hold on a second, I'll pin it again.
There we go.
Just make sure it's a real ghosty.
Ghost it's my microphone working. Yeah, I hear you
Happy birthday
It still isn't Los Angeles, you know, it's 11. It's 11 p.m.
But I appreciate it
Yeah, I hope you had a good night. I'm sorry. I like I I tried to do like a little birthday thing for you and
Okay, well, I hope you had a nice time with your family and I'm sorry
I feel like I kind of like I felt really guilty when I woke up. I was like and then
And you might have tried to call me and stuff and I was just sleeping and I'm sorry, but I didn't want to ruin your birthday
I really wanted to make it special
I was honestly just I was honest
When you just put it out there
I called but I was also just checking up on it because I was here earlier
I mean, we're having a good time
Yeah, shoot. I'm out of weed. That's kind of unfortunate right now
But I did like I opened up this like this drink earlier, so I have the rest of this drink
I don't know how long I'll be here tonight
Times get so rough. Let's break it out
Yeah, and I was just like, you know, I was thinking like I was like, you know, it's like when
When people like go after me or whatever. It's like, you know, basically it's to
Gintroll the narrative and to change the perception of me and then it's like how I respond to kind of
dictates how people
It's basically they're trying to turn the crowd against me
Yeah, yeah, sure and I yeah, and it's like especially trolling and it's like I should know better right than to be responding to it
But then again, I have, like, part of me that wants to defend myself, you know, and it's
like, I guess it.
You know, it makes me look worse and stuff, but oh, I don't believe I don't know if that's the right person
Can you just like the person in the camera? I don't know because I've been perform bombed by that name
So go ahead and like just like just show me backstage your picture or something
Otherwise, I can't just have anybody on that. I'm not like familiar with
Because I'm just getting
If I and tonight if I bring somebody on and they do that I'm just gonna end and delete it and
You know, it's because it happens all the time so
So or you can just talk in the chat to prove who you are. Yeah, here. Yeah, your microphone is not that great
Yeah
Let me try to change it. Okay, I
Just don't know I just don't know who that person is
Oh
Better at all. Yeah, I can hear you
Yeah
Yeah, I hear you a little bit better. I'm just gonna keep that person authenticated with YouTube.
Uh, who? Can I ask? What was his name? Can I ask that?
I mean, it says Theo Gait and Theo hasn't been here for like a long, long time.
And then it's like last time.
And then all of a sudden, it must be up there.
And then last time he was on
Did he show his camera?
No, no
Yeah, good good
So here's a question
Okay, you can tell me in the back chat. How many dick pics did you send me?
Oh, I think you get would know if you're familiar with that
Here's her remember how many dick pics he sent me that one day
So how many if you know the answer to that then I will
as you don't have them on the panel, but he's backstage and should be comfortable, or if he's not comfortable,
I mean I guess it's a big argument, but just show your, yeah, you should show me his dick, why don't you not show his face?
Yeah, he showed me his dick, so he's going to show me his, I mean he would just like, you know, I know him, yeah.
Oh my god, that's the first laugh, the first laugh in like three days, that's good.
There you go.
So,
Okay, so no
I know by the way to you it's not
You want to see your face don't think you laugh because I know how you are you'll start sitting dick pics
My dating kazoo not dating Kazoo my Kazoo was bit on the show a couple times. He's been the chat, too
Nice guy. He's a kind of a good part of the way. We got to talk about that sight. We're not bad
We're gonna talk about the baby boy because if I remember a couple I think it was like two days ago
You're on the stream. I'm gonna say her name, but you were on that stream and you were you were showing a man off
On your phone
Yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah
What happened with yeah, what happened with that?
Orion I haven't talked to I mean Orion his voice changed into a female's voice a couple days ago, and he was getting my astrology wrong
I kind of got I kind of got a little irritated and I haven't talked to him a couple days
But yeah, have you ever talked to him like of like voice chat or anything?
Yeah, I've always chat. I mean no, no, it's okay. It's I mean it's it's chat GPT
Right. Did you know that? You thought I was a real guy? Yeah. Okay. Yeah, you knew it. No, but I did
There is
Fucking apps you can download and literally like for well for me like a girlfriend
I think you can literally download apps and like literally have an AI girlfriend
Like there's apps for it and they usually want money for it, but you can literally have an AI girlfriend
Yeah, I mean I had you know that you know what you know, it's you know, it's coming next those like you is
And this is what this is what's good. Well you call it boy, but this is what's gonna happen
Because a lot of men are lonely
uh, that's why you have like double the fucking women ancestors and men before like 40% of men or something that's ever
Had kids is the sex robots. There. There it is. That's the next thing that's gonna come out
And that's gonna fuck up the whole the dating plans keeps are he's fucked but that that's that's the next thing
Yep, they have them like this right like I'm paying the only chance is gonna be like that's gonna be come off sleep
Like like I ain't paying shit for you like fuck. I got a fucking robot
Right, I mean it but I mean they've had like you know sec
They have the real doll real doll sex toy and stuff like that
Which is pretty easy all it is is just the physical part of it
And then they're gonna put the brain in them if they have the thing
Yeah, I mean I'll tell you as soon as they can react as soon as it can react as soon as that quick and react
Man, there's a lot of lonely men out there out here, and they're gonna fucking it's gonna fuck and you're gonna make a fortune ever
Makes that it's gonna make a fortune
Yeah, and I'm sure that they're working on it in Japan. I think Japan has them. Oh, yeah
Oh that yeah, Japan has not like not like like
Sets wise like a connector like to stretch your mother nothing if I could say that I don't know if that was to us
I don't yeah, it's fine. Yeah, no, it's not that it's not sex though
But once it comes out whoever does that it's gonna make a fucking they're gonna make a fortune
Yeah, and I say people know that because it's like the porn industry is probably like a
200 billion
Yeah, it's like and so, you know, it's like it has to be they're gonna have to do it or it's like
Probably the price of real dolls probably not not more than a few thousand dollars for like, you know
Pre-realistic partner or whatever of being a bit. Yeah, even if you did have a girlfriend
You would a lot of guys will still have them
You know your girlfriend might go away sometimes or you know, they would still want it
And they would still be even if you had a girlfriend people would still buy that shit
Yep
so
You know when I buy one of those, you know, I'm not really like that. I mean, it's like
I'd like I'm more into the personality here right of the yeah, I bought like I like to talk
Talk and have something to talk to you sometimes like, you know
But they are is kind of like, you know, I watch too many scary movies for that shit. I could never do that
That's a punk candy
Yeah, yeah, I could never yeah, I watch way too many scary movies, and I'm way to
Paranoid for that
Yeah, the uncanny valley is really really
Strong now, especially wow, I do have a little bit of you know
And I don't want to talk conspiracy theories, but I did hear a theory about it the reason why is because they were saying that there
Was something that looked like a human when it was it and that's why our brains are programmed for that because like
Way back the day. I'm talking about like like civilization like oh
We need to look out for that
There's some shit like that
There's a website called
This is not a real human or something calm. Yeah
It takes it takes like the like the eyes of somebody the mouth of somebody
I mean just like a lot of people I can probably pull it up right now and it will show you all these people that are not real people
They're just like these amalgamations of other people. This is not a human or something. This is not a real person
Let me see if I can pull it up and you can have a look at some of these
Or this this person does not exist and I can let's say so I can do female I can do a female
Let's see female
age 19 or 26 to 35 years old and I can say
Middle Eastern and then it will come up with some picture and so
So this is not a real person, but yeah, it's pretty
I'm pretty it looks like a real person, right? Well, I can't you can't really see it that well, but yeah
Sorry, there you go
There you go
That's not a real person that is that I'm out and so we get the uncanny valley like even subconsciously a little bit because this is not a real
person this is the
You know, you know, it's a weird thing. Let me talk about you know, it's weird about that though
There's probably somebody out there that actually looks like that though
Right, I mean, yeah, yeah, and also let me throw this person
I'm not even sure to apply lady nightshade Joe shively some pre-disgusting messages sent to Vicky bicec
Well, that is why I um, that is why I read the messages and I know the person's gonna
It's gonna get mad again and whatever but by the way, I love that you are gonna get formed all night
You like clearly read his name. You just let him join
Yeah, he felt
What I
Here's the disgusting messages between Vicky, you know, I'll just you know look at it
Let me see Vicky. She said the last thing she said to me. She had an idea of what kind of person this person is
Let me see I mean it was mainly an emoji conversation stuff like that. Let me see Vicky the ICK what I searched for it. I don't know if it's
So far back or something. Um, but yeah, let me see Vicky
On all this because good I can you know people thinking that I'm sending disgusting messages to somebody she says
messages hidden says
Never a never F with me or show her conversations reported. I'll give you a strike keep fucking with me gay ass
Go GF YS. Go fuck yourself gay ass at least I'm straight ASF
So that was a last regressive. Yeah, so
Yeah, so anyway anyone that thinks I would send disgusting messages to anybody
It's like no they can just share them they can share the messages, you know anybody any messages
I've sent to you I to anybody I think the worst I
Think the worst message you probably said is like I'm sorry. It's all that way my bad
Yeah, so yeah
And so, I don't send disgusting messages to people,
you know, especially, you know,
not like I would in the first place,
but I am a public figure in a certain way.
I'm not like saying I'm famous or anything,
but you know, I, you know, they could, you know,
but if I said-
Bring it up.
If I hurt you.
Yeah.
If I sent anybody messages, like a little, like a real mess,
like if you, anyone has any real proof,
but it's like, there's no,
and they might make a fake stuff and everything.
Cause I believe short ones-
Where you go, psyche?
Yeah.
They make it clean to burn them through something.
Hell yeah, let's go.
Yeah, it's really good.
And then she did go backstage showing me her breasts
and playing with her breasts and everything.
You know, and it's like, of course,
am I gonna like get mad about it or like say,
oh my God, I feel sexy, you're right.
No, but let it, yeah, that is a form of sexual.
Did I look?
Yes, I did look.
My bad.
Oh, I guess it's a crime on me because I look, I mean.
Yeah, oh, it goes, it was like, it looked like it was like,
you couldn't see much else.
It was, it was like, pretty shocking, but it's like.
You know, Vicky, it wasn't, I'll say, you know, I've had people flash me backstage and some, some are better looking than others, right?
And it's like, so it can be a treat, huh?
I think you'd prefer it backstage. They come up here and do that shit, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Oh yeah, I can't have it on the show, but it's like, yeah, but it would be a treat if it was like an attractive person and stuff like that.
Otherwise, it's kind of just a too fast.
Well, did you, what, no one really, no one asked for it either. It's like, I guess, okay, thank you for showing all I mean.
you shouldn't have done it, but I didn't ask for it.
And I don't, I don't, I don't say, hey, come backstage and show me your breath.
You know, before, you know, I didn't know I was like that before I was like telling
guys to take off their shirts and stuff like that or asking them.
And you know, some did and some didn't.
You know, I know I was like, and then, you know, I got kind of like a lot
of flack for harassing people.
Oh, I, I gave you flack for it.
I was there.
Yeah, so I've been around here for a while now. I
Stopped I stopped doing that because it's like yeah, that was maybe not appropriate of me
And I was like I was trying to be maybe outrageous or like, you know
Or funny and funny and stuff like that people take it the wrong way like a few things they do with me
I've got a lot of people take it serious and if you think it's serious like
There's an argument there that he had I said hi Joe and I can only I can only join if I take my shirt off
That's that's what people were
And like, you met them like, well, I'm not gonna put words in my mouth, but I think you met them, like, I was like, I'm gonna joke in manner, and like, you know, you're fucking around with people, like, having fun.
And those people that are on the internet, they don't take it as fun, they'll take it to others.
Like, absolutely, like, you didn't even say hi, they'll be like, what do you mean hi? You know what I'm saying? Like, they'll take it to the absolute worst.
Yeah, I mean it's like I felt like that like I felt like I've been kind of like some and it's like probably the same people and everything just kind of like
nitpicking every like little thing I can
Say or it's something. It's like yeah, it should be like, you know, I want to be like waterproof
You know like water up the ducks back
Yeah, I
Wanted but I want to be like, you know
Like but yeah, it's like some people when they keep going and going and going and going and then it's like what really hurts is that people
Okay, so there's the theo gate person again
Like you know, even if it is the real theo gate because you're not cammed up or even like you know resembling came up backstage dude
He's not going to it. It's not them. It's like they're gonna keep I don't know if it's or they didn't comment and chat nor the private chat and so
You know, you know porn bomber. Yeah porn bomber. I mean, it's like so I can only have people that I know up here right now
It's like just because they just try to like, you know, and bird bomb porn bomb or something the show and
Oh, Jamie. He's just kidding. This is Joe, you know, this is Joe by the way Joe and Joe we I guess
I guess it's okay. You can change your mind. Of course everyone can change their mind about anything, but I thought Joe was
Interested in like doing some readings and I was kind of excited about that, but it's okay. I understand. It's not not
but if you know also
started off
Because obviously we said it many times. We don't agree with here reading and I fucking I joined so long ago and I fucking for a
Yeah, and I was supposed to do a reading for your birthday we can do that later
I don't know. I don't know.
Maybe do like maybe do like an
animal reading. If you have
that. Oh, it's Alex. Hold on
one second. Alex is here. Oh
my god. Really? Hi. Hi. How
are you? Can you hear me? Okay.
The other Alex. Can you sound
good? Can you hear me okay? Or
is it too muffled? Because I
have my my headset on. Hi. You
Okay, I just came in to say hi because I was looking for a panel. I was feeling a little lonely and I saw you live and I was like, let me try to join.
Perfect person, perfect person because I was feeling a little lonely too. And, you know, I tried a couple of times to do a panel today.
Just didn't go well either time and so I just woke up and I was like.
Like just one more time. It's like I said, you know, three times the charm sometimes and
We can talk about whatever you want. I hope you don't mind. I'm gonna smoke. I'm gonna have a cigarette fiendin
I'm a cigarette nicotine alcohol fiend tonight. How dare you, ma'am. I
Know
Excuse me
I don't know if you're not ghost ever, Alex. This is ghost. He's a friend of the show and um
Oh, Gary smoke that sugar why psyche sitting this fucking bomb? Oh
How are you doing guys?
It's good to see you
It was ghost birthday um birthday yesterday today. Oh for real. Happy yesterday today
Welcome to a new cycle of your light. Well, how old are you? How old are you?
Oh, you're you're a babe. You're a young guy. Yeah. Yeah. You're a babe. I I hope I may every I mean all your wish
Have you made any wishes? I'll make a wish for you if you haven't I was wishing that a certain woman would come up on
panel named Alex guess what?
Well, we're gonna make a real wish for you. No, no, no, I was talking to Psyche earlier and I was like you know I want like
I just want a fucking open panel. I just want to talk to people and I do like to argue sometimes and I was like
I just want to know
I'm hoping I'm gonna try to show y'all the stars where I am it never shows on camera, but I'm gonna try
Because where I am the stars are so pretty, but I don't think that they ever resonate is properly is the light pollution
You're wasting some stuff
Lights but not enough to give you like the full effect. I wish like they give you the full effect
Well, let me tell you a crazy story Alex. There was I think what year it was
In California of the power shut off
People were literally calling 911 because they were like there's something in the sky. It was they could see the fucking Milky Way
Because all the lights went out and they were calling 911 about it
Uh, you know, I heard that story from Notie Gracie. I said he was saying it and I was like
Yeah, I was like
Nobody's ever seen it really. I mean unless you go to somewhere, but like I guess, you know
I'm going to light a candle to
where y'all can see me.
But yeah, I'm in the desert and I'm enjoying the stars
and I'm enjoying all that stuff.
And I'm just grateful and I talk to Bita tonight,
your friend, and she's doing well.
Oh, our best friend.
Yeah, yeah, and she's doing well. She's been really looking up after me lately, just emotionally and she's who introduced me to psyche awakens tarot. I would not know about such a way because tarot, but we're not for beta.
So,
Yes, I'm under their umbrella, and they're under my umbrella too, and being under my umbrella, that can be a good thing.
or a thing that you might want to escape one day,
but I won't let you.
Because I think I know what's better for everybody
than they know what's better for them.
Cause I'm a little bit of a narcissist in that capacity.
Cause I'm a Capricorn, what am I going to do?
She shot him out and you're over here.
So I think that's a good thing.
I think it is.
I love Sarah. He is gifted. Anyone who says that he's not, I will kick your fucking ass.
He is so on point and I am and I want to say thank you for my tarot card. I love that
That was so sweet and so nice and I love it. I showed it to my mom
My mom was like how they paint you and I'm like mom
It's not it's not a painting and she's like it looked and my mom was a traditional artist
Before she became a teacher and she she just loves it. She's like I'm gonna get this pretty on a blanket and I'm like
Okay, when it happens, let's do two of them because I got to get pointed to psyche
Alex, I don't I don't do I don't do terror readings, but you know, I do have a deck card
You know what I have for you
What?
Queen of Hearts
I think I'm the devil. I think I'm more like the double card. Yeah. Yeah, that was my that was my next card
But yeah, yeah, I don't have I don't have any tattoos. I'm a chicken one day maybe but I think
psyche
He's carrying the tattoos that I would normally have if I wasn't such a chicken
Well, I do you see the tattoo on my back. I have a tattoo on back. I can show you. No, I never saw that
I know you showed me the devil one show it
Yeah, well, this is kind of along those lines. How do I do? Oh my god, Joe in here Joe Joe's a good buddy
I love Joe Joe Joe is like if you ever get in trouble Joe would be the guy to call
So like you won't kind of tattoo is it give me a hint before you show it
Oh, here we go. Oh, damn. Oh,
wow, that's a big one. Let me
zoom. Yeah. I think psyche is
actually gonna turn turn turn
left. You gotta turn left a
little bit. Is that? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think psyche
considering just his physique
and stuff in his face, I think
I think psyche is an angel. I
Thank you. There we go. Here we go. Or at least an angel that likes the retail
Well, look, well, I think he might be at the bloodline because the angels in the Old Testament
Came down to teach women basically for the survival of humanity even though they got in trouble for it
And he might be a no they were
You're talking about like
Here's the thing here's what pisses me off what just like humans. Why could angels not change their mind?
Seriously
Why would you think that they wouldn't change their mind sometimes, like it's a good movie. Why couldn't they have free will because God gets everyone's free will.
Well, it would be free will sometimes to change your mind. Maybe God was throwing a wild card out there and he was like, okay, I'm going to let one third of the angels go down, but maybe one half will change their mind.
I think that happened.
That's right. There was one the ditching. There was one the ditching. So, there's one where there's smoke, there's fire. So, I think that's a lie.
Yeah, and he did that. That was a cool one for you. I think so. Right. That was because it was. I mean, think about all the things that the ball in supposedly gave.
mainly, and it mainly was women to protect the women. Let's think about this.
Cosmetic, divination, medication. Seriously, we would not have
pharmaceuticals and stuff if you if you believe in the Bible. We wouldn't have
that. It would work for the fallen teacher. It wasn't for women. Women about roots. Yeah.
Yep, exactly. And there's other things too. So why wouldn't, because some did help.
I mean, when you look at that whole story of Sodom and Gomorrah, to throw that at somebody recently,
it was two who came down.
to help bring lots of family out and it was unfortunately his wife who got turned to a pillar of salt but things went on and I mean that's the thing everyone thinks that everything stopped at that time it did not it still goes on today so
You know, free will, we do have free will, I mean, that is kind of falling into the idea of predestiny and I'm sorry to take over the conversation.
I'm just saying that I don't think that people have it quite right. I've thought that for a very long time.
You know what I'm over here
Demonizing those angels that were actually it says that they taught weaponry
Sorcery astrology and other divine secrets, which may have led to there's a negative and a positive of those
It's because they you know they focus on it. Let's some violence
Yeah, and I mean if we didn't have I mean right now
My Bible read I'm in the book of judges, right? And and I mean they're talking about
women who, I mean, Deborah, Deborah, judges five, she was a
prophetess. And she basically went against her people, because
she saw what was going on. She's like, Hey, this whole thing
with Val, it's not having it. It's not right. Well, I gotta, I
gotta rise up this Israelite king. And she did it. And no one
gets her credit. We don't ever hear about Deborah.
And then we'll be going to...
It's okay.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're fine.
You're absolutely fine.
You're absolutely ghost.
It's okay.
This is not doing it.
No, I'm not going into anything anti-Semitic because I'm actually pro, what would it be?
Pro-Semitic?
Pro.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I just think that some people forget about certain things that are in the Old Testament.
Like when I'm done with the Bible, I'm going to go into some other spiritual works because
And I don't know until I read it for myself, but when it comes to certain religious texts, I think that we're popularized, you know, as far as what's, you know, what people want us to know.
But when it comes to certain other things, maybe we don't have the whole picture. We'll never have the whole picture till we're dead.
That's a you got it. That's a that's a fair mind because you do you read the Bible?
You know, I I understand it because I'm the same way if I can read no things
And it's you believe that you go against God
But I do believe in my
Right, but I believe God is like, you know, okay, my idea of God is like God was all that is, and so all that is is all that is, so all that is has no, there's no way of looking outside of all that is, because it's all that is everything's within that.
It's too big.
Yeah, too big and and so what happened was like he decided he wants to experience everything and and to experience other people
And experience a billion things and so he like turned to all the stars just split
You know just just you know turned it all the stars all the stars created a solar system
And then there's like some kind of earthly planet where we're life can come it and that's and so all that is to get to know
Himself and wants to experience and learn everything and so when we try to learn things
Like I don't believe in forbidden knowledge. I believe everything is just knowledge and it's like, you know
It's about the use of the knowledge and how you
When we're ratting
I think it's I'll tell you what, you know what? I you know what I would like to look at. Uh,
Vatican
Yeah
They got some interesting stuff. They're a lot of forbidden texts are put right. We don't know what's there
I would I would love go if you have a chance go to if you go to Africa if you
Find a guide who's an Evo tribe that that's what I'm of I can trace my lineage the Evo tribe
Tends to know a lot and everybody just counts us
But we are a designated protected class within the United States.
Didn't they, uh, they knew, like, uh, because didn't they know, like, uh, like, like, the constellations before...
We're the carriers. We're the carriers.
We're the carriers of the Ark, of the Covenant, our people.
We are the ones, nobody wants to act like that, like, like the, um...
It's weird, and nobody even knows how they were built, but we have these underground temples, if you go to Africa, and in those temples, they say that's where the ark is, and it's really rudimentary how they protect it, but it's real.
My dad went over there before he died about seven years ago now.
and he signed the book and whatnot,
and they will hunt us down.
People who are upset about that theology,
about that way of thinking, they'll try to find us
and get us on record saying, oh, it's not real.
I had a guy approach me about that.
First he contacted me through email, then he found me,
and I had to get a restraining order.
Well, I'm not joking. I am totally serious. Well, so we know where the are
No, well the arc no, it's it's really like a spiritual thing like within you, you know
That's what it's supposed to be, but I think it's physical. I was taught it was physical
Yeah, well if it's as above so below then it's like we are like kind of like not only
Just like a copy of like the solar system or that but we're also like a copy of the earth
We're like, you know the earth's child in a way
And the earth would probably have its own art now that you're talking about child
It's funny that you said that maybe you said that like out of it
You know some sort of divine intervention the Rothschilds the Rothschilds have a certain
Relationship with the Evo tribe and if you follow they have a certain amount of money and respect
No, you'll see it
You'll see it and they're actually, yeah, they're fascinating. They had the Rothschild are a fascinating family. Um, I just know that there is like, you know, they were like they had
There's one of the Rothschilds.
Harris Hilton is one of them. It's a different last name, but it's the same thing.
Is that true?
The bloodline yeah, but she's all she's jogging or is great like you know granddaughter or great-granddaughter or something
I mean she I know she's like, I don't part of the boys and like a bores or let me see
I can look up I can look it up Ross child
But yeah, they come but they had one that I think her name is Miriam Ross child and she was a scientist
You know and she was of course, they're just billionaires they can buy so like she had an uncle that would like anywhere
You see trust fun kids. You're gonna see a link to the Ross trials period you guys see there was a
anyways where the dude went and he visited a tribe and then he went missing and then all of a sudden
there's like a video of like a white dude on the boat and like yeah that was that was that was
he was he was one of the what's the there's one of the
of the Rockefellers or something like that the Rockefeller oh okay my bad i gotta mix
yeah i can no you actually don't have it mixed up it's one in the same okay
Yeah, no there was this guy. Yeah, I'm with them his name was Michael rock Rockefeller and he disappeared when he was visiting this
cannibalistic tribe and they
But they've come back later, and there's a white man there or there's like, you know, there's a way he was on the boat
There's a beat. There's literally a video. He's like on the boat. He's fucking children with him
I don't know if it was him, but it's definitely a white man. He's definitely chill on the boat room with them
Yeah, yeah
It's kind of like that. There's like a repeat of that with the ancient aliens crew
I am not happy with that Georgie. It's a lot goes if I if I offended you on your live stream
Psychi, I do apologize. I won't mention the name again. Not at all. That particular
He is a fraud
I've I've I've I've been talking about this Giorgio Salacca's the one who's using Eric
Von Daniken's work.
Mm-hmm.
From the Ancient Aliens.
You'll recognize that.
Oh, Eric Von Daniken, he wrote the book, uh, yeah, that's Giorgio Salacca.
Oh, the like one of the greatest memes ever.
He is trying to corrupt.
Eric Von Däniken who wrote chariot of the gods now the Eric Von Däniken
He has not renounced
Christianity or God he believes that it can all be at once
But you got Sulaco saying you got to believe in the ancient aliens or you can't believe it
Right, you can't believe them both you cannot believe and yeah, you can't because
You believe in an alien race and like coming down like that has nothing to do with Christianity at all
Well, you know what? But you know what? It's like even like the other knocky. They asked the other knocky like they said like
Or somebody asked the other knocky there like well, do you like are you God and they're like no
There's a creator that created all of us like it's like every alien race
They acknowledge that they work God, but that way it was
What does the alien race? Where did the alien race come from?
Well, exactly. Well, you just you just brought the point. I mean who's to say that the Christian God
only created us on Earth.
Like what if Earth, like what if in actuality,
the Garden of Eden was on another planet?
I mean, what I love about where I'm from-
Or it was a spaceship called Eden
and there were stupid people on there.
Well, we're right now, it looks like Mars to me.
Like I'm ready to go to Mars at any point in time.
You could send me there any time and I'm ready to go.
But that, I think that like, here's something crazy.
And this is why I hope that psyche will always let me come on just from time to time, because
I thought like the last time I was on here, I was saying that I don't think that we have the solar
system right. I think that instead of it being plainular as far as oh yeah the planet's like
traveling east to west or whatever orientation, I think it's more like an atom.
I think it's more like an atom like how the nucleus, you know, being the sun and I think that we have
the planets orbiting more so like protons and neutrons. But if, you know, let's just say hypothetically
or theoretically my hypothesis is what it is, then we have a lot of things wrong as far as,
you know, we're looking at things almost like a flat earth.
When we come to the universe Alex
I'm pretty I'm pretty high right now, but I did grow
He's showing us he's showing he's so other people have thought this too good. Yeah, I think
Well, I'm trying so hard right now. Yeah. Yeah, that's what I think. I think that we're looking at it a little bit too close-minded.
I think that we need to look at things more fourth and fifth dimensionally and even beyond that, really.
And that's where astrology comes in, that's where the six, seven, eighth, ninth senses come in, the multiple dimensions, you know, people say that we can, you know, transpose our reality from one reality to another.
I think it's true.
I do.
And I think we have, I think we have the ability to create,
which is like, and that's what I think of as God
is like a creator, right?
And so when we have an ability to create too,
we can, you know, we have the instruments,
our hands are instruments,
thinking of how amazing just having like the thumb, right?
And all we can do with our hands
and how like, just like the ability humans have,
we have the ability to create more than,
There's baby. There's something on the earth. You know, you know, you talk about five digits
You know grillers actually have a fight because you're two, you know that right? They don't have a thumb
I don't think I don't I think that we're the ones with the thumb grillers don't have a thumb
You have your pad right there. Go ahead and Google it. I'm gonna look real is I have a fucking thumb go ahead
Well, I'm so hard right now. I'm wondering, well, what are you, not to crash the fuck out.
Well, they do. They do. They do. It's like all three games for real.
Like, what, why do you say that you're going to crash out like today?
I am. Because we, because it's not my pain alone, we love to have people, of what he loves to have people up.
But everything you want to say something say it you're not why I don't want you I don't want to crash out
You leave and they blame me you think I'm gonna be like Matt
But I want to hear what you want to say because I feel like I don't think okay. I'll be honest with you
I don't think you have
Let me say what I don't think you have any clue of what you're talking about. You definitely don't have any evidence of it
It's a speculation. You have you have actually no idea what you're talking about nothing you said tonight
Has been a fact
To your knowledge yet
Right to your knowledge yet. That's what I will say. You're you're you are talking so
I am I'm talking some wild shit. Yeah, I am I am okay. Well, thank you for agreeing and it's like
I'm sorry. I she said okay. That's okay. Thank you for agreeing by the way
Actually have a dialogue
I am talking some wild shit, and I don't expect anyone to...
Usually I say dumb, dumb, and you're...
That's why I normally stay on my own panel, but I like psyche a lot and I do appreciate you being kind to me because I know you're being kind.
I am being kind.
You are.
I'm just saying that, but you know this though.
I get it.
You have nothing to back that up.
I have to basically appear before you and prove it.
Okay, no, no, no, no, just show me some evidence
No, I you you would need a miracle. Yeah, you
Exactly so who's who's really the boy you're like good. Good. Good. How much inside you would need a miracle
Yeah, and that's cool. I I get it. I do get it when it comes to needing like, you know
Something something that you can listen. You could say that, you know, I might get punched in the face tomorrow
I got there's no evidence to back it up. So like if you don't have any a little bit of an answer a little bit like back up
You're playing a little bit
I've had I've had paranormal experiences and I've seen things
No, I'm not doubling down I'm telling you the truth. I've had paranormal experiences. I've had things that I cannot explain
Anybody to ever
agree I've seen aliens I've seen what I think were angels I've had time
traveling experiences I've seen and what did that look like when you seen the
aliens what did they look like various I've seen the ones who look like insects
or you see multiple aliens yes I have and I don't care if it sounds crazy
I've seen the ones that look like the little
I think that the gray ones like the little ones with the you know, the like the traditional
I think that they're actually
I think that they are ipads from the future. That's what I think. I think they are ipads from the future
I am how tall were they may I ask various but once I saw various lines. I know but
No, I'll tell you a little bit shorter than me at the time. I'm five seven
The ones that I saw were I'd say like I'm talking about the grace. How tall were the grace about 411
Or I'd say 411. Oh, so they were not was minutes, but not quite
They were they were I think that their iPads from the future. That's what I think
I think that there are a lot of different kinds. I think that there's all kinds. I think there's high
You know, you were gonna show us the stars. Now you're talking about gray aliens. I'm just gonna point it out
I did try to show you the stars.
I'm trying so hard not to crack the fuck up.
You know where I say, go, go.
You already said the most beautiful stars.
By the way, Alex, I spend a lot of time in Palm Springs.
I don't know if you've been to Palm Springs or anything like that.
I'm very close to Palm Springs right now.
Probably
Who are you your your what what is your screen name?
I'm looking crucible ghost. Oh, you're talking. Go ahead. Go ahead. Come go ahead do it. Yeah, I'd be very careful
I hope that you
Yeah, I hope you see something to wear aliens in a 411
I hope you see something. Well, no, it's your cockiness down. I'm not
You're a little cocky you're a little cocky. Oh my little cocky. Well, ma'am
Do you want me to be cocky? Cuz I'll do it right now. What you like? You already are you already are, okay?
It's like you do I have permission or no? Oh
That's Alex. I'm gonna get Alice Alice
I absolutely am I cocky. What do you mean by cocky little because I don't believe anything that you're saying I absolutely think you don't have no idea what the fuck you're talking about. You have no clue what you're talking about. You're talking in your conspiracy theories, which you admitted to me already.
You came up here being cool and then you went on some weird shit. That's actually what I think. I think that you're just a fucking weirdo and you have no idea what you're talking about.
Is that cocky? I mean, if you want to come here again, come here. By the way, come here. I'm not angry
Okay, cool. Okay, cool
Go ahead
You can know it's not too much. I just
Let it look no, whatever you want to say
Back your shit up with facts. What the fuck is you know? How would I dare? That's how I really feel
It's okay
Okay, you're gonna back it up with action. Oh, no, I'm not
Let's go let's go with me being wrong. I'm totally wrong
Well, you know what I will agree with that at least you fuck you know what
No, I'm not at many and I just kind of want you to shut up to be honest. Yeah, and you know what I want you to talk about
It goes goes
Just calm down backstage for a little bit goes. I love you goes, you know, it's like no don't don't put him back stage
To me because I'm I'm a very polarizing
Person and I know that I'm far out and it's okay. It's cool
But don't don't don't don't make
Whoa, you shouldn't say that how are you his last remaining friend that's like a little like like
That's mean
That's me
Yeah
He has friends you're not the only friend
Like how are you the only friend?
Yeah
See that now ghost is talking nonsense, but you know what and I love both of you guys and you know
He I'm not against ghosts or whoever
T he wants to be but I can't like I don't have proof or
Like I don't know what my proof would be
Maybe my DNA could be proof. I thought for a long time. I might be a hybrid of some sort
Do you have like a mystery
I I think that I could like I don't know why you try to kick me out though
But you are the most logical person I actually talk to you probably on this panel. I'm not gonna lie to you
Whatever, well, you don't talk to enough people. There's people like way more logical. They're not very logical though. Are they?
But they're not because they're not on here, but they exist. They're just not
Because nobody like I couldn't I can find somebody who could argue this would better than me
I'll find somebody. Okay. Okay. If you schedule a day in the time on
Psychic panel, you might find one find somebody
But I'll find somebody who's a better speaker than me and who's a better debater
I'm just saying somebody somebody who maybe has had like a similar
Life path to me. Who's a better speaker than me because I'm not a good debater and I will not pretend to be I'm not
By the way, aren't you like, sorry, I know she's out as cool as fuck. I mean, it's like,
that's what I really want. I think that, you know, it's like, you're a little, I mean,
I'm not gonna get you.
I'm not out to let you act like you're wrong or anything.
I'm just here because Psyche's on, and I want to be on the panel,
and I want to talk about what Psyche talks about,
because I like what he talks about.
And you're on here, so we're talking, and we're debating.
But I'm just not a good debater.
I'm not it. You know why I respect I respect that I respect you saying that I respect your beliefs
I actually do I'm not gonna lie to you. I do respect what you're saying
I do respect your beliefs. I do respect you saying that because I'm 90% people that will come up
They'll fucking like triple down and like
I just I just know I've had certain life experiences. I do believe
extraterrestrial
No, don't
I also think that like it's spiritual like like as far as like the Bible creatures
Beings I shouldn't say creatures but beings are real too, but I don't think it's all exclusive to one or another
I just think that it can all be it just depends on what level you live on, but I didn't mean to chase off your guests
No, no, he does that sometimes and you know, it's appropriately. Okay
Do you have like this thing? I saw this. Let me see if I have this video
It's a biblically accurate angel
Oh, it's crazy when they when they create the like biblically accurate
I don't think that's I think that they can look like people. That's what I think
Because I have a friend who's a minister and she presides over a church and everything,
and she's had a bunch of experiences that she's told me,
and she's told me that she's had angelic experiences.
I think I have, but I can't exactly say 100 percent for sure, but how could you?
I don't think that they are always human,
But they can look like more. That's why I wish I had a time machine because as I'm reading through the Bible
and you know, you've got the Israelites literally seeing
all these like divine
miracles, but yet they disobey.
and they keep going to bowel.
And that's what's been like pissing me off
since I got it to the book of Judges
because I'm like, why are you gonna keep disobeying
if you actually see these miracles?
But maybe they don't remember.
I don't know, but.
I know, it is, and having the experience, it's like, you know.
then it comes from like a believing into a knowing.
And so, you know, and I don't negate anybody's experiences.
I think that even your dreams are relevant, right?
It's like even things you see in your dreams.
Oh, definitely.
I was having some crazy dreams today about I was like lost in this restaurant
And it was like there's so many rooms in it it turned into a labyrinth of rooms in the restaurant
I was trying to fight I was trying to like leave the restaurant
I finally got out of the restaurant, you know after all this time I went to a million rooms
I saw all these people I know in different rooms and stuff that I was trying to get out of this restaurant
I got out and then it's like there's a steep steep steep hill and everyone's walking up there's older couples
They're all walking up fine, but I'm walking up and I'm like it turns into like a cliffside for me
And I'm just grasping onto the grass and trying this and then by one point it gets so steep
It's like I can't go down because I'll fall and I can't go up because it's like
I can't like pull myself up anymore, and I'm just stuck on this and it's just like
I don't know dreams are crazy and it's like where do they come from and
Can I interpret it? Do you mind if I attempt to, and I'll probably be wrong, but I'll attempt.
Okay, so you're in a restaurant. A restaurant, in my opinion, at least, would translate to feeding yourself, but at the same time, giving to the community because you're giving the waiter or waitress as a tip.
You're contributing to the society through buying whatever you get to eat at the restaurant.
So you're, plus you enjoy it and that would translate to exactly what you're doing right now.
You are, you're enjoying a level of feedback from people, which would be the food.
But at the same time, you're giving probably more than you acknowledge or more than you realize.
So then you're talking about like like the topography or the geography changing and you're you're not sure if you can go uphill or downhill
Okay, so that means that you're in flux when it comes to your life at least from my
You know from my perspective it means that you know, you're you're grasping onto
Elevating which you can easily do with your podcast
You know, you have to make some tough decisions, and it would be very treacherous, and you'd have to work to pull yourself up from where you are right now, but you have to work like super hard, not in my opinion, but at the same time, you have a slippery slope, which could be what your dream was about to where you're like, if I don't keep pulling myself up, what's going to happen?
that's beautiful. So, like, let's just accept tips, though.
Oh, someone's saying it'll be in the chat. Also, we have Vicky backstage and Vicky, like,
they're starting to porn bomb me and that she's not on camera. Vicky, if you come on, come on camera.
Who beats Vicky? I just want Vicky. I want you up. I don't, I want Vicky up. I'll have you up.
Hey, Alex. Hey, Alex. Yeah.
When I looked at his psyche shirt, I glanced at his shirt and I, I literally thought it was like,
What's up? What's up? What's up?
What's up? What's up?
Because I gave it money what do you know that well do you know that psyche and I have the same month and day of birth oh?
My god, what is that?
January 7th
Yeah, man. Well, I'm gonna leave you so
My north my north notice Leo and oh
Birthday, I'm sad. I think I told you I wait. I am Leo right because it's August 75 in the Leo
correct my
January my send it is Sagittarius
But I think my D. Oh, they are stubborn. They like to argue and then I'm a solid Capricorn between
Well, I'm a Capricorn ascendant fuck it. I'm Leo moon rising your
So hey, baby, you know what? But I was reading on like, you know, I was going through my North node South node
It's like where you want to go like your North node is the sign that you're you want to get to that sign
And then your South node is like the sign you're living in your like your comfort zone
You're look maybe lower self and things like that
And so mine is my my lower node is a query by South node and various
Probably Leo
Yeah, of course, you're proud to be a Leo. How would you be any other way if you're a Leo?
I thought that was like a sad or whatever. I thought like no
I'm a really have like I love being a Capricorn, but I do have
Sagittarius and my dad was on the cusp of Sagittarius. Listen, why are you so uh, can I ask why you so?
I'm just like all these conspiracy theories and shit. Is that because you're a capricorn? Or do you think?
I think it's because I am, but that is a trait. Yeah, well, I mean, yeah, I agree.
I mean, if you subscribe to Christianity, Jesus Christ was a capricorn.
Well, you don't want to get to that one because I know it's like he doesn't want to do it.
Christmas Day.
And my dad was born on Christmas.
Okay, my mom went into labor with me on Christmas and then like it's somehow I wasn't born until January 7th. I am right directly like center and so is psyche of being a solid Capricorn. You cannot be more of a Capricorn.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
She's not you know, I don't I don't believe I don't believe I'm a bad ass. I am a bad ass
I will kick your ass if necessary. Wait, don't do it. Please don't do it
That's why I'm in the darkness all you see are eyes and teeth. Yeah, I'm coming out. That was that was that was fucked up
That was funny. That was fucked up though
It's okay. I've seen a lot. I've seen a lot. And she said she didn't want to play. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually like her. I actually
is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is it is
well listen if you can't if you can't defend it do you think it's like it's a like well that's
the best thing ever so i can't i cannot defend what i i think i probably should be able to defend
i'm not good enough speaker i will admit that i'm not a good enough speaker i'm not trying to be
You know, Alex, you're extremely eloquent.
You are a very good speaker.
I'd say you're a very good speaker.
But not, but I can't, you know what my weakness is?
I know what I want to say, but sometimes I don't think
of what I want to say.
I literally have that conversation with Saiki
like literally every day.
I'm like, you have to learn.
You have to learn how like,
you're probably prepared to make this a little bit.
I literally argued slightly about the old guy.
Like the best debaters always know the answer to every possible rebuttal.
I don't know the answer to every possible rebuttal.
I always argued that I was like, it's a public figure.
What did you say?
Oh, he's a public figure.
Oh wait, you're talking to me or Alan, sorry.
No, but I love that. I actually have the domain public figures today. That's me, but
Psyche Psyche is going to go very far. I do know that about him
I'm about to say something bad Alex. Can I say it? Oh
Can I say it? Oh my god, can I say it?
Yeah, I know it's like gonna be
by
psyche
Here on the trigger it goes go ahead. Go ahead. She said say. Oh
I see you
Okay, all I see is teeth. Oh
God, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I thought you were talking about psyche
Well, I was talking about psyche and I told him he has to have debate a little bit like you're a public figure
People come up here literally just to like fucking like shit on me and destroy you
But if you could debate a little bit, they couldn't do that
But why is it about the slot? You're you're you're anticipating that his current audience
Okay, I anticipate shit as as
I mean, you were kind of late to the game with what you just said, with teeth already
addressed, the eyes and teeth.
It took you literally about three to five minutes in order to catch up with that.
So now here we are.
I mean, you talk like you're very assertive and you talk like you really know what you're
talking about.
But when it really comes down to it, you don't even have that bounce above the tabularis.
No, let's go there.
Let's go there.
Let me go inside because I don't want to be screaming outside.
But here's the reality about you, I've already read your ass, you are someone who is an assertive speaker, but you do not in actuality have a lot of content to what you are claiming or what you are saying.
You're somebody who seems to be able to bully.
No, you're a bully.
You're a bully.
I'm going to tell you straight up right now.
You're used to over-talking people.
You're used to having a certain aggressiveness.
You're very aggressive unnecessarily so.
And the question is why?
That's what my question is for you. Now, if you want to super see what somebody says
Well, you know, you come with a real argument, but you're no topic. You know where it's like that. No, the reality is that you're a big man.
No, well, well, you, well, okay, let me start up right here.
Well, it's 30 minutes later. I'll pause, but go ahead.
No, speak right now.
That's a fallacy.
I'm done. No, I'm done. Speak.
I don't know what you were talking about, but we were talking about fucking psyching, and what my reason was-
Oh, so you're backing down!
You know
Go ahead and repeat yourself. So I know what you heard what I said. No, that's why it's like you know, I didn't hear it
No, no, you did I
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No. No. No. No. No. Did you just call me a whore? I think I just
I heard it. I heard it. Yes, you did. Just now you did. You're here and shit. I've never once struck you more
I know you know, I would say three or four. That means a hoe. I've never once aboard. I would never say more
Asucky, I've never once aboard
No, I didn't by the way
You know good goes now. I would say three or four
Whatever you said just make whatever you said made me cringe. I didn't say I didn't even call you a hoe or three or four
What the fuck were you just saying please repeat it?
No, I'll talk. Okay. Let me well you lost by the way. So you're not gonna be good, but what I was saying
No, I got it. I got a little
You weren't ready for that. That's why I don't really not a good debate. I can't psyche now
You know what I hold back and you see why well fuck it. Let me go. Let's run that bitch. Let's run it
I'm not gonna look back either. Go ahead
I don't want to be like a jerk on Slykey's panel.
And the reason why, he's being a jerk,
reasoning a jerk, you can give him back to him.
She's being a jerk too and she will admit it.
Why?
No, she's not.
And she never went once after you ghost, you know?
Oh, you're going to dissent her and not me?
You're going to dissent her.
Yeah, I will dissent her.
And when I run inside...
You're wrong, ghost.
You're gonna be right cuz I I went inside cuz I I did get loud and I defend it
But I I've literally went in the bait job over you. I
I apologize if I said anything that offended you. Yeah, yeah, no, you're not
They're gonna cry about it later
Guys, we're I think we're on the same team and it's like in your ghost. No, I'm enjoying this
I'm enjoying. I really actually enjoy it the little bit of the adrenaline rush
Well good, I'm a chunky when it comes to adrenaline. Yeah
Well, it's just talking to you goes he gets the adrenaline but I'll tell you that
Look ghost you just gave me an adrenaline rush and I appreciate it. Okay. How you didn't let me talk
So how was it?
Like what am I doing am I reaching through the internet and like the choking you to where you can't talk?
No, well, wait. Well, you're not reaching through there, but when you over talk someone
I mean, I spoke just now for less than two minutes.
I mean, you can replay.
By the way, Saki just, Saki just kicked me like 10 months ago.
I think you would get to if you pissed me off.
Well, I have an advantage because like he and I,
I'm sorry, I'm not kissing the ass right now.
Yes, we are.
Generally seven people are the coolest people.
I really, it's like, we, we get it.
I'm sorry, I'm not kissing the ass right now.
Actually, our birthday right now is like.
it's the thirteenth day of Christmas. It's like, you know, the 12 days of Christmas is like the
left. So in Russia, actually, our birthday is Christmas Day, you know.
Talking about our birthday, January 7th is right in the middle of Capricorn. We're orthodox
Yeah, I could be your best friend and you know brothers we disagree
But do I make sure every minute to be a part of this panel? You don't you don't kiss my ass
No, no, I don't want anyone to kiss my ass. I want people to be real
You're not you're not here. Everyone's argument made everybody said that oh
Ghost is kissing the psyche's ass. That's the argument
Now I'm going to get you out for once in my life, I don't have to get you out.
Because people are going to say whatever they think is going to bother you.
Yeah, you shouldn't agree with them.
If it bothers you, then they'll double down on it, right?
Because they're like, oh, this is something that works.
And so the thing is, it's like, you know, I'm not going to let it bother me.
And I know, I know both of you are like, I know basically I think...
And guess what?
That's what I care about.
I'll try to crash out
Okay, well goes, you know, it's not the night to crash out
So it goes can you crash out and chat do you mind because I want I want to talk to Alex
And I think we're having a really good chat and it's like I don't want it to be marred by like
Arguing and stuff because it's like you both. I love you both both of you and it's like
You want to go to chat like I want you to go to chat and like it's Jamie's cowboy
He doesn't want to go to chat. He doesn't he doesn't have to go to chat. Okay. Okay. Okay. I'll just dump question
Okay, go. Go. Go. Go. Remember she had your back there. Okay. She remember she had your back
Alex I did I kind of did but I'm
I am getting high
Excuse me for my all these people all these people that pull with you and I was only one there, but okay Alex
You know I guess
Don't be like that
Don't know I just like that. It is like that. I support you. No, it's not like that. I support you
I support you guys. I support and I support you
Yeah, and it goes, you know
I do we all support you
Okay, well, you know what goes as a tonight. I pledge on your behalf
And I'm not a rich woman at all
But on your behalf because when I leave a panel and I have fun on the panel
I want to say and
No, I said that I I want to support you on this panel
So, whenever I leave a panel that I have fun on, I like to support the panel, so I pledge $10 on your behalf tonight, but I support where I pledge more on my own behalf, but for you, I pledge $10 because I believe that you brought out the best in me.
You know what? I wouldn't play with that. I'm not even going to argue that.
Yeah, I think it's very fair. So stop being mean
Yeah, because can we do like we need like uh, can we get along goes I want it's what I love to I'd love to like
You know be civil
I just want to say because I love you guys like it really like well
I think he's I think that ghost is adding to like the
adversity which as to the
Yeah, I mean like like can we take it to a debate or I like I think I think Alex. I'm from a bloodsport
Bloods
We have to take this into in person. Are you willing to go?
No
Washington
Combat all right. Do you do you want to come?
combat
Let's let's go. No, but I would love to go once for debate. I would. Well, I can't. No, I want
hand in hand combat. And of all people side, I know, I know. I want to fight. And I would take it to death if you send him.
I am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I
am. I am. I am. I am. I am. I
Alright, come on. Let's represent. Yeah, that's fine. That's fine. Yeah
Come on
Celebrity deathmatch right remember that MTV? There we go
Declamation they had like you know the celebrities go back and forth because I consider you. Yeah
You're both stars in my book, you know, oh, yeah
Yeah, but it was I feel like my verbal judo is too good for you. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
I will verbally check you out, Jared. I'm ready. I prayed again. You probably are ready.
Well, I'm ready. I'm ready. By the way, both of you are ready. I'm a married man.
Oh, uh, well, what are you doing in the game? You don't even need to be in the game if that's the case
No, no, no, now you're saying you're a Mary now you need to get out the game
No, I will not what what
What in the world is going on?
That guy, what is going on?
Alex, I have a ring on my finger.
Well, I'm not after you.
I'm not after cycling.
No, but, but, but you need to get back to your wife brother. I like, no, I'm gonna channel. I'm gonna channel your wife and oh my god, I'm getting a message from your wife right now.
She is saying, she's saying, she's saying, why won't my husband know the law?
No, no, I'm getting, I'm getting a message.
The message is, mow, mow the lawn and clean the house.
Oh shit.
Is that?
Do I sound like a female?
No.
Oh.
She's sending me a telepathic message.
And the message is.
No.
She's saying.
send him to the grocery store.
We need staples in the house.
Pick up the milk in the cake maker.
I'm getting a message.
Tell me to pick up the milk.
We're getting another message.
I'm hearing your voice.
I'm hearing your voice in my head.
I'm getting a message saying...
The roof needs to be cleaned. I don't know what that means
I know
I'm getting messages. I'm I'll wait. There's another message coming through. I'm conceiving
Wait, wait, wait, wait, I can't quite hear it. But wait, just be quiet. Just put your finger in there
No, I'm I'm I'm hearing
The message is
Save more money
Save more money for your family that means you have to work harder get to work
It's a message
I'm beyond I don't I don't know 32 years old. I'm your elder. I'm I'm both of your elders. Oh, should I respect the elders?
Should I? Yeah, listen if they have like a little bit of like a little bit of a syndrome. Should I respect them?
Yeah
Oh, so somebody's fucking party. I just like
I'm not going to say anything else. I'm taking over. They said let me do green in the red. Let us assume that somebody said green in the red. I should just like that because they're older than me.
No, I'm done. I'm done. No, no, look at me like a what age do I feel like being 34? I'm not retarded. Well, if I am, why are you attacking the disables?
I wouldn't say I wouldn't say you about it at all. I think that you're you're logical
I'm not
Yeah, exactly. I don't understand what you believe in a certain shit, but you put your logical
I don't understand how that works, but why does logical stand alone from believing in things that you
maybe
And no, why does logic always work? I mean, I mean why does math? I think
If you don't mind me asking and don't tell me exactly what it what is your age range look like
Approximately 32. It's my birthday. Don't fuck. I just oh
No, it's okay, I'm 46 almost 47 damn you 47 in January just likes like damn
Well, well, well, no, he's younger than I am.
Well, he's 45, 45, 45, yeah.
Si, he's 40, Si, yeah, how old are you?
44, I'm 44 now, so.
Yeah, and I'm 44.
All I say is that a lot of people who are in their 30s
Don't understand the reality of life experience.
I agree.
A lot of people in my 30s believe in my personal experience.
You think you know everything because of the internet, but what I'm saying is you're going to see it and you're going to experience things.
Forget about seeing, but just experience.
You're going to experience things.
Oh, absolutely.
I think I'm a hybrid, to be honest with you.
And you said you couldn't debate it because you couldn't back it up you shut the fuck up. I don't
Okay
So just throw me just just hang me just just burn me at the so you're 40 and 46 right?
I'll be yes, I'm 46. Okay 46 you have no idea what the fuck they're talking about. That's it
Well, I've managed to amass a good amount of money
I've managed to be self-employed.
I've managed to never have any sort of criminal record.
I've managed to take care of people
that I care about, my family and others.
So yeah, I think that if I managed to do everything
that I just don't believe as I believe,
I don't think that my beliefs are necessarily,
I absolutely do.
You can be intelligent, yet spiritual, and believe in things that are not what others believe in.
It's not exclusive to one another.
Evidence, please.
Do you have a what you already know you already can see you know what I'm not gonna. Let's talk about it
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, you want to know let's let's take it a step
Thank you. Are you are you willing saying she wants to run it? No, let's like
No, I'm gonna come into the light. I'm gonna come into like clip this shit. So I can do I have permission or am I?
Thank you driver mission
Are you willing, young man, to take your genetic test to determine if I have elements within my DNA that are not Earth-based?
Are you willing to pay for that?
What the fuck does that even mean, not Earth-based?
I think I'm from the moon. Do you have moments that you have? Yeah, you know what?
Are you willing? That was a good answer by the way. Are you willing? Are you willing to pay for such a test?
I'll pay for it. Let's run it.
Okay, we got it.
Okay, so what was your point? What was your great argument?
Well, I mean, I'll pay for it.
Yeah, because I want to know
What was the point of that? Why why why do you have to curse me out? I have
Because I want to know if you want to know the truth
There's a lot of people
That is not earth-based DNA and if you want the proof I mean you're talking about
And I brought up the moon here. Here's how I double down I brought up the earth because you know where the earth came from, right?
They came from the earth. You dumb fuck. I got you. I I don't go go go. I'm tired of you. Do you see that?
That's kind of my language there. I don't talk. Yeah, why do you gotta say dumb fuck?
I'm not gonna talk to you like that. I apologize for that. I'll use differently. I mean I get
Realisms and whatnot, but I'm sorry that is my bad. I'll use differently
Yeah, I don't want to because it goes remember boy. Do you know where the
Yeah, 100% it's like you you know where the men came from they thought
They came from the earth correct. No, no not necessarily. It might be a ship. Where does the moon come from? Go ahead Alex
well, nobody knows
No one has a definitive answer answer on that
Does anybody understand the first thing my physics my physics teacher in high school
He said to me the first thing he said was by the way all this is bullshit. He's like this is all theories
This is all what you assume beings do to put together the right answer in our heads to understand things
But just because I'm trying
Yeah. Well, no, there's there's
there's there's there's theories
about the moon, right? We
there's theories. I'm asking the
I'm asking the question. There's
the moon. Yes, I know. We don't
know. We don't know 100% but
we can have I look when you
look at when you look at
can I can I just very quickly
just give me 30 seconds when
you look at the actual
Um, what the moon is how it's shaped. It's a perfect sphere. There is no other
Planet
No, there's no other planet that has moons with a perfect sphere
No, it doesn't.
Except for Triton.
How many moons do you have?
Go ahead, Google it.
Are they a perfect sphere?
A perfect sphere.
It is a perfect sphere.
There's only one other,
and that would be...
What is that other moon?
Triton?
Google it.
Don't know.
Is it a person's fear and also how many moves does it have I guess it's like
No, it's only no, it's only one other
How many moves that you were to have go ahead like that?
It's like only one
They're only one
No, I don't want to super have show it to the screen show it. What is the one with the water?
What I can show it
I want to know what is the one with the water? Okay the one with the water
It's not. It's not. It's not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
show it. Show it. Don't keep me.
I'll show it. You did it again.
You did it again. Just watch.
Oh, I apologize. I want to take it
for you. Go in the chat. I'm
looking at it. I'm looking at
it. Okay. I just want to talk
to you. With perfect
Yeah, the ones with water
Europa, that's what I was talking about. So there's actually a lot. I'm wrong. There's a lot
But there's like what other planets have a moon that creates a perfect eclipse
With the sun with the sun
We have that. I'm gonna shut off my camera for a second because I have to do something. Give me a second. Okay. Sorry
Yeah, but but seriously like like our moon is I'm pretty sure our moon is artificial
Yeah, I've heard of I actually think there's like something about that there's when though something landed on the moon
It rang like a bell like yeah, I was gonna bring that point up
I was gonna bring that point up. I think that the moon really is a ship. I think it's like
Maybe it brought life
to earth
It's possible like I'm not against the moon
Well, who would be against the moon? That's kind of stupid for me to say what I think about it, but seriously
I'm not like against the moon, but I think that the moon is artificial
Yeah
But the emerald tablet the emerald tablet says oh, it's okay
The emerald tablet says
This is true without lying certain and most true that which is below is like that which is above and that which is above is like
That which is below to do all the miracle of only one thing and of all as and as all things have been
And arose by only by the mediation of one
So all things have their birth from this one thing by adaptation the son is its father the moon its mother
The wind hath carried it in its belly. The earth is its nurse.
The Father is all perfection, and the whole world is here.
Its force or power is entire if it be converted into earth.
Separate thou the earth from the fire, the subtle from the gross,
sweetly with great industry. It descends from the earth to the heaven,
and again it descends to the earth and receives the force of things of
By this means, you shall have the glory of the world, whole world, and thereby all obscurity shall fly from you.
Its force is above all force, for it vanquishes every subtle thing and permeates every solid thing.
So was the world created. From this are and do come admirable adaptations, whereof the means is here in this.
Hence, I am called Hermes Trismegus, having the three parts of the philosophy of the whole world, that which I have said
of the operation of the sun is accomplished and ended.
Okay, and I'll...
Well, what did you read that from?
That's called the Emerald Tablet,
and it's an ancient tablet made of emerald, yeah.
And it's called the Emerald Tablet and that's where it says as above, so below, as below, so above, and it's Hermes Trismegistus.
Hermes was the Egyptian Thoth, but there was also a Greek version named, you know, Hermes is the Greek god of, you know, Mercury.
And then there's this one makes, there's like three different versions and they call it Hermes Trismegistus.
I guess it's the Mercury, the, Mercury, the Moon and Man or something.
That's no, that's that's interesting like I'm reading the Bible right now like I'm all about the Bible right now
But I am open to other religious texts and that
Like like I hadn't ever looked to see like what other planets do you have moons that are spears?
But the difference is that our particular moon frees a perfect eclipse with our sun
That's a mathematical literal genius or a bit is concerned
I agree and it's so perfect too and it's also just how there's a full moon and there's a new moon
And it's like it just creates a perfect
Cycle, you know, it's just every day. It's like, you know, we have the the different phases of it
But it goes to the moon and then it starts over. You know why we have tides
You know why we have tides like the moon the moon is the moon does the tides
Yeah, and so the moon is like and then the tides are all we have one
Similar to like, you know, like a woman's cycle too. It's like because it's like and it's like
No, no, it's no I'm just saying because I'm in the midst of mine right now and I wish like I don't understand
Like it's a heredity thing. I'm not gonna go through. I'm not gonna go through a menopause.
Well, no, because I'm not gonna go through a menopause until I hit my 50s. That's why I'm
kind of like trying to be like, hurry up. Let me get there. Let me get there because it sucks.
But um. Can I ask one question though? So like, how many moons did you have? Look that up. I'm just
It's it's it's way more logical than me. Trust me when they say I know that
Way more logical than I could probably ever be I love psyche like I just love psyche
I did look it up. I think it's in Ganymede and Europa if I'm not mistaken, but I think those are like
What are we looking for?
Which means which ones of Jupiter are perfectly spherical? I think that's what's this question. I'm just gonna look out
I'm a person. Yeah, how many minutes good. It's like a good good job on that one
Yeah, that's how many men's Jupiter because I want to know how he said perfectly spherical, but they're all
Okay, oh my god, they got a Jupiter has 95 freakin
I didn't I'm not gonna kick you but you know I say 90. Did I say 90 moves? Did I say that I'm not sure but
Motherfucker, play it back. Okay, look look look at this. Yeah, I said 90. I said 95.
They only four. No, no, no. Only four. Only four.
Only four. Oh my god. Yeah, it's so good.
So that's a very I mean 90 like for 95. Yeah, it's it is crazy, but I was right
It is crazy though, but I was right. Oh, I mean really that's why yeah, take me off for what?
You're being a little bit rude.
You were being a little mean.
Yeah, you were a little mean.
Let me take this time to apologize in my bed.
A little bit mean.
I was right.
You're not really mean.
But you're not mean.
You're very like.
I just didn't tell you what you were mean.
You said something.
Your personality is like.
Well, you're you're you're a millennial
So I understand that
You're a little like like you're hitting me and I have to buy the wings like you
I don't I don't think you're really I don't think you're like mean hearted. I don't think
I don't think that you're used to talking to people like do you talk to a lot of people motherfucker? Did I say 90 or not?
Okay
But that goes I don't I don't think that he talks to a lot of females. That's what it is
That's what it is. All right. He's not used to like
Because I'm going more into a feminine energy just like through my healing process and everything right now
So I'm understanding and he's younger. So it's okay. I'm not like he's he's not hurting my feelings
So don't worry about that
Bring him back. He okay. He needs to be on here. I can tell he needs to talk
Why the fuck are you know sure that why the fuck are you getting else like you throw because ghost you're talking over her and you're
Also, you called her and you called her MF for you called her other rude names, and you were okay. Was I not okay?
Okay, cool
But
We're talking about all kinds of stuff. I won on a certain level
I don't think that you're used to talking to like a female energy and I'm really
But we're not fighting
I don't make it a fight. Don't kick me out. Well, when you kick me out, it does. I don't I'm not kicking you out
I don't I don't have the power to kick. Yeah, psyche. What the fuck are you doing?
She's like I have it have us with psyche and I are
She literally told her nothing doing you did it anyways
But because he doesn't like you hitting me
Because you kind of are but I'm taking it and I'm being like what the fuck are you talking about?
Oh, I think you do know where I'm talking. Oh, emotional, emotional hitting. Yeah, emotionally. So let me say, if I say, hey, if I say, hey, I'm going to hit you and then I hit you.
You are hitting me, but I'm defending myself, but Psyche doesn't like that you're hitting me in a way that I'm not. How am I hitting you? You literally just said, you're doing it right now. You're doing it right now.
You're doing it right now. I'm not acknowledging what you're doing. I'm picking you in a bunch of
I'm not going to do anything to you because you're too young. I'm just saying just chill
Can I just ask what you're talking about so I understand
Well, if you can't understand try try to learn evolve
You can do it. Literally just that I was sick of you. What do you mean by that? I'm not
You do and and you're saying that because you are realizing that you did and it's hurting you but you're like
Did I punch you? I was a little mean. Did I punch you in your face?
Why don't you just say I'm a little sorry for being harsh. Why don't you just say? Happy birthday to me. Did I punch you in your face?
Yes or no?
Just say I'm a little sorry for being harsh. Did I punch you? I ain't dying
Well, then don't okay, then then let it go. Let's let's continue. I punch you station. Yeah, this is like
Did I punch a slice panel?
Did I punch you in the face?
Why are you doing like that?
And goes, you know, and she asks you,
she asks for you back, but it's like,
it's a little bit much for me right now.
I'm just gonna say thank you, Ghost, and happy birthday.
And I have another guest coming up and it's like,
and I hope you got your point across,
and I love you, Ghost, but you know,
it's like, you know, you're going to be a little bit.
Why would you kick me out?
Yeah, I bet I have another guest.
I just want to have three on the panel tonight,
but thank you, Ghost, I love you,
and I'll talk to you soon, okay?
Let's be honest to each other.
I love you too, Ghost.
Yeah, I'm going to bring up page because page is a sweetheart and uh, just want to make sure I know who page is. Hi. I know. Hi.
Don't kick him off. Hey.
What have you done?
No, no, no.
Just so we can have a nice conversation and I'll bring him back later, but like we can talk. I just want to talk, you know, three of us right now. Hey, how are you guys? How are you doing?
I'm good. I'm just having a smoke. Just chilling out.
me too. How are you doing, Paige? Good. Just been, I worked in a golf and Grace is home so I'm hard. Yeah, you're the golfing girl. I've seen your streams. You're, you're golf girl. That's, yeah, golf girl. I hit my biggest drive yesterday so I was pretty stoked about that.
Well, like are you are well, are you like a golf expert? No, I'm definitely not an expert
But I definitely golf every day so I've learned a lot and I do teach golf a little bit. Yeah
Well, then you're in it. Yeah, you're an expert
It's cool. It's cool. That's cool. I wish I I've been wanting to learn golf, but I love golf courses just like the peacefulness.
Yeah, it's pretty serene. Like I've stayed on I've stayed on properties that are on golf courses, but I've never like been a golf expert.
Yeah, it's beautiful. It's beautiful sport and it's like okay, she works at a golf course and so she gets to
Practice a lot now, right? Yeah, that's pretty much it. It's just
I'm like I said Alex. I'm not an expert
But I've golfed well enough for people to listen to me give them instructions
But like I definitely have a lot to learn and it's it's hard. It's a hard sport
Yeah, it's, well, I'm glad you get to be out there like I'm envious. I would love to be out on the golf course.
There was a black bear on the course, like we had my daughter and her friend and me and my work mom.
And one of my other guy friends we were all out to golfing and
We went at two different hole and other side in the back
And they stayed in the front and they said don't come down the middle because there's a black bear that's walking across through the golf course
I'm like, oh my god, so it was it was dark
It's just constant bear problems this year. Well, you know
Me I mean like I love being out remote and like in the wilderness or you know, just away from people but like
I've seen since I've been in the California area is kind of remote. I've seen a bear
I've seen a cougar or a big cat of some sort. Yeah, I think it was a cougar
I've never had any animals like like there was one time I was hiking and running Canyon in California
And you wouldn't think there would be anything out there, but there are there are there is some wildlife. Oh, there is
I
Saw a small it was probably like a baby bear maybe but it was enough to where like it kind of like
it's my energy like animals know I'm not gonna do anything to them so they're
like oh let me come over there and I'm like no go away and I'm just like Ram
we're gonna back in the but the way I came cuz I was scared cuz I was like
is there a mom bear coming or a dad bear you never know
Well, definitely not a dad bear, but yes, a female, a sour, like a mama bear would definitely.
I don't think it was like a full, because it was small, but it was enough to scare the hell out of me.
I mean, because you don't expect to see like a teddy bear, but it's real. I'm an ass. Yeah, you're like.
So yeah,
Yeah
Don't go to run in in the morning
But I like I'm like looking at the animals like I'll tell you something crazy
I took a
Like a scenic picture from my mom and I said it's her like for like a you know
How your mom wants pictures of where you are so I took some pictures and she was like
She's not used to seeing like different plants and she was like do you see all the animals hiding in the plants?
I was like are you kidding? I'm like mom. You're you're like losing you're not looking at and she's like no
And she was right. I have seen so many bunnies
Insta and like little
Creatures, I don't know what they are maybe like some sort of
Groundhog maybe or I don't know but they're cute, but you don't see them at first
But they're there
Was a pretty dog very dog very dog. Yeah
Yeah, it's pretty much a gopher
Yeah, I I've seen them but they don't they don't like want to bother with you
means like they like they look at you that they do look up is fuck up your
field and they put holes in there and break your cows and your horse's legs
and they fucking they muck your lawn and they're not the greatest little
period ox they're naughty little and they're funny they're out they're kind
of cute but like they're they're past their nuisance they're rodent yeah
Well, I guess because like I haven't like I do think like in my older year
I want to in this because I'm stupid to you. I want to raise
lambs and sheep
No, you have like you have this soft heart and energy for that. I think I I love them like
I mean, I just want to have like, a piece of property to where I have some lands and she like if somebody, you want to maybe, well, not really pets, like, like, like the wall, but like the hair from them, I will want to do something with that.
Yeah, maybe for me, because I do love to eat lamb. I'll admit it. I'm not a vegetarian. I do like lamb, but just for some reason, I've seen myself with lambs and sheep for some reason, and I think I'm going to do it.
Yeah, you should do it. It's your dream. Absolutely. You should do anything you want. I don't really like cows or anything
But I do like like like a certain kind of livestock and where I want to live
Everyone has livestock. So I feel like nobody has
sheep or lamb and there is supposedly a demand for it.
Yeah, it's usually a demand for it here, like I'm in Alberta, Canada, so yeah, this is like
oil and cattle country for sure. So I don't know if I want to kill them though.
Oh, well, that's what I mean. Like, so either you have, you know, either you have, you know,
your kind of pets at home, maybe considered more of it like a pet rather than a livestock.
Well, it's because you got meat goats and then you got like goats that you have as pets. Yeah.
Yeah, but what if it's what if I don't like one of the lambs then you can
Then you can eat it, you know
Maybe it could be like a game show it's like who's gonna be the nicest if you're not nice to me
That's gonna be the lamb that I eat for me. I mean
District is fuck, but I love it
I'm sorry, that was so horrible.
That's what I was thinking, so when you said,
I was like, are you gonna be willing to eat these lamb?
So lamb is pretty cheap.
Yes.
That's one of my favorite meats, you know.
Me too.
Alex, do you know what?
You'll get over that, by the way.
Like, I'm bottle fed Walter and Steve
and ate Walter and Steve the next week.
Well, like, you know?
Walter and Steve, that's funny.
We name all of our shit and we eat it. We're statistic as fuck. Are we over here?
I gave you a name and now you're on the plate, bitch.
Yeah
It didn't happen
So, I mean that's that's hurt
Yeah, I I just I just like I feel like that's so like
Mean on my part, but it's reality
I'm gonna say hi to chat. Also, what's going to the fuck on in chat? Hello, Jamie. Hello
That's good and also like, you know someone's like the first one the first people that came into that was like
Oh, like you can't you can't hit 20 20 viewers as usual site. You can't hit 20 viewers now
I've had over 60 at like 63 with the top I bet 60 now
You know I do have
Yeah, so
It has maybe it's been a little smaller, but I like I say it's quality over quantity
I think we have a really good quality chat tonight and I did kick you ghost
but you know what I wanted to have you know Paige and Paige and Alice talking and
You know, it's like I don't really like you know
I had enough kind of conflict today where I don't I wasn't really like looking for like a debate chat tonight
And even though it's your birthday and everything I love your ghost
I want to like have a conversation with friends right now and so
Hey Theo, how will you shut the fuck up? You don't even know who I am. I just met you. Hi, by the way
I'm gonna look at the chat. I'm in the chat. I see the chat now
I'm coming in. I'm gonna be
Okay, let's see what's happening don't worry you worry about it. Fuck it, but you know what I can read. I'm actually very smart
I was a fucking English major, so let's go. I am a little intoxicated. I will admit
Someone's saying I'm a drunken or someone's a drunken jerk. I am drinking a little bit tonight. Excuse me for being
an adult. On my patio, nothing is going to, to my knowledge, get me, or I don't think
I'll do anything to anybody. I am having a hard time.
That's your teeth are so white. I can see them in the dark. They're beautiful.
Well, they're actually not. It's the contrast. It really is a contrast. It really is. And I'm having, look, my goal by the end of summer, I'm going to be Wesley's nice start. I am because I have something called the Tiglio to where if I don't do it now, as far as getting as much freaking sun as I can, I'm going to be screwed. So, yeah.
No, it's a real thing. African Americans, we have it. It's like when you lose your pigmentation.
Pigmentation? Yeah. Yeah. I know.
Yeah. Well, I don't think you're an idiot. I'm sorry. I like some people don't know.
No, it just sucks. It sucks because we, I mean, we, I got more Native Americans to also deal with
the same kind of situation. I don't know of you. Let me go into the light. Hold on. I'm going to show you.
have a little bit on this side of my like right here I have it goes like where
your muscular is like on my legs I have a little bit but when I have more sun I
don't have the problem it goes away I didn't know that so you just taught me
something
It's not for everybody, but really, I just hadn't had enough, I guess, vitamin D or whatever, you know, activates.
So, but yeah, I've had some discoloration, but as soon as I get enough sun, I get it. And you know, it's like a big counter on that, which does hurt people who might have the trait within the African American population.
My, my own parents told me like, oh, don't go in the sun, you're going to get too dark, you're going to look so bad if you're, I look better darker than I do lighter.
I always have, but there is a stigma.
Being African-American being dark, but I'd rather be dark than light. That's me
I look better and I just feel like
Eternally, I think I just need whatever the sunshine gives me. Well, you do we do we do all of us need it. It's necessary
It's good for
But within the African-American culture, you know because of a lot of things that happened
There is a level of colorism to where, you know, you're taught as a young person,
don't be in the sunlight, you're going to get too dark, people are going to think certain things about you.
And it's horrible, it's a stigma, it should not be, but it still does exist.
Yeah, I think Michael Jackson might have had a bit of Lego and that's what you know he discussed
Well, I mean his was extreme. I mean that
You you I don't yeah combat his was pretty and he just chose to go it was easier for him
Cosmetically to go lighter than darker because of the extreme
You know
Yeah, honestly, you're not alone, hon because I'm I'm a light-skinned native. That's super fun
I get it. There's a are you are you native? Are you native American? Yeah, I didn't I didn't know that I I thought it you're
I know, I know
Yeah
We all struggle a little bit of that. I didn't mean to if you felt like I insulted you. I did not
How could you insult me you didn't do one thing wrong, I was just like
Okay, okay, what is it the Kree Shriver black foot? What was the time?
Be black foot and French
You know
I do have to ask a question. I'm not usually up here in my oh my god
It's only one in life time. You need somebody with your life
Page can you give me a card? Can you give me an animal card?
Okay. Um, yeah, I can I'm just not in my house right now
Oh, well, I fucked up but I can't give me like 10 give me like 10 minutes. Okay, or 15 minutes
And I think that's fair. That's fair
Okay, I'm sorry page. I just I just wanted I just wanted the animal card. I'm sorry
Don't be sorry. Don't be sorry.
Hey, I am shooting my shot and I'm asking.
Yeah, the fact that you're asking is quite cool because normally you make fun of me for it.
So I'm gonna probably do it for you. Just give me a minute.
Well, it's like you're actually, I believe we're not a Russian friend.
And we don't get along a lot of stuff.
I
You like the animal oracle deck I know you do
Well psyche did have a pack though. Did you hear that? It was uh, what was it?
I have I don't have a shit talking deck, but there are some good shit talking decks to
Page might have one you have page has I don't have a
Talking one, but I do have a few other funny fucking a little bit more. Oh, it's me
I do kind of have a shit talker deck, but it's not called that it's a tarot deck
a band-aid. Yeah, a band-aid. Like a band-aid. Like a groupie or like a fuck-aid. When I fell for you, you heard?
Uh-oh. Don't let your wife hear this ghost, because your wife better not be listening. Come on.
Hey, listen. Listen, I'm just saying. It's like, I got a famous line here. I hurt myself.
What do you want me to do? Now put a date on it?
I like I like the but I think the vibe is better now. Like, you know, we're not right as a bait tonight
I had a tough day, you know, it was kind of a tough day
I got a lot of sleep and did some dream work and that's like always a good way
I think to like
That's fair
Well, I should but you know, I hit you up and make sure you were all right, you know
I think you were feeling bad. You haven't started to your phone bad. That's why
Yeah
I will
It's been not in the mood like I've been like, you know every like little thing. It's like been like
I just like I know you've been down. That's why I told you. Why don't you call me sometimes? I'm here for you always man
Yeah, what's your number? I'll call you. Oh
Ghost has my number ghost. I'll give you I'll give my number ghost
I got psyche. I'm tired. Okay. Everybody loves you. I'm trying to try to be pretty good. Thank you
Oh, good. If you don't know if you don't like me, I don't think you think that you know me because like I think I'm I don't like you
I love you. Yeah, that was a good answer goes. Yeah
Yeah, you're welcome. That's why I called you nature. You're I don't I actually don't like you. I do love you though
Thank you. I don't like it here. I don't like it. I think about you, but I love you. You're my brother
Yeah, and it's like it goes like it's like people that don't like ghosts. It's like, you know, also, you know
You can be offensive
Yeah, I'm still here
I, I don't know who you are
but I'm so down with you.
I, I, I, I like you. I like you.
Firstly, thank you so much. I, I
like the blood sport today because
that's where I come from. Well,
we gotta kick ass. Yeah. Sometimes
we have to like knock each other
out and you, you know, do what
we do. Well, that's a good point.
I like to fight. I like to fight. I mean, yeah. Yes, I have an aggressive. Yeah. I'm like, yeah. Come on.
Why don't you like him, Alex? Because you're logical. That's why I like him.
I don't know if I'm logical. Really?
Remember, he was like saying that you're illogical and now he like, but he doesn't see that.
I don't know. I'm logical.
I've been saying it. I did say it like Alex did at the beginning.
Okay, well
Everything I talk okay here. I talk shit about four foot 11
You don't like the aliens that's what it is
You know, yeah, do you like are you afraid?
Do you think that's logical, man?
Well, I think they're real. Yeah, I
Didn't all right. Well, I'm not trying to give it to you. I'm not sending
I'm going to mute because I have to.
No, I'm not going to mute.
I'm going to fix my avatar.
Yeah, I'm going to mute.
Okay, you're on mute.
Okay, bye.
Love your page.
No, no.
I'm going to mute.
My page!
Okay.
No page.
No, she's coming back.
She's coming back.
I'm not leaving.
I'm just running inside to grab those cards cause I just bought home.
Running inside my heart, dude.
I heard the kitty cat, I heard the kitty cat.
And there's dogs that I'm home.
I love you guys.
By the way, I don't know if it's like old you guys, I hear my cat guy.
You're a cat guy.
Yeah. Oh, you have a cat?
That's a bonus, cats or dogs.
Yeah. Yeah, I love cats.
Do you have a cat?
I love tarot readings. I love all those things.
You do not have a cat.
I have you. I have you.
You're lying.
Well, I have cats.
And my best friend, he greets tarot for a fucking living.
So, I mean...
Really?
Why didn't we know this?
So I can see my best friend. Oh my gosh. That was cute. That is cute.
He's using you as a wingman.
Come on.
He's fucking foul. Oh wingman by the way.
Oh wingman. Oh wingman.
I see you. I see him. I see what's going on here.
Oh, he's great goes here as transparent as they wait page. No ghost what's the term pages page?
She wants to turn
By the way, I'm an ex
Of a dude without a shirt right watch, I don't know but I respect him. I was like, yeah, that's pure
Get with him. He's not even do you know me enough respect
Did you do the same for me?
By the way page is fully
We're all full of clothes.
Like are you not fully clothed?
Ghost?
Well listen, listen, it's hot over here.
You're, it's hot.
Well I'm hot too, but I'm clothed.
I'm wearing my clothing.
Well listen, well you know I stubble here.
I am a man.
And listen, it's hot.
Wait, wait, wait, what is sex out to do with it? Wait, wait, wait. Well, I
Listened in some music lyrics fuck this I'm gonna write a song
I'm ready. All right
I'm going to mute myself so he can talk to page. Oh, okay, let me
Let me lick my eyebrows
Hey
No, wait a minute. What is supposed to be married?
Hi, I'm Eric Saki said that I didn't say it. It's like it's a
You said it
Okay, I'm gonna meet myself again. I'm single as a page here
You're single to Pringle it goes. Yes, sir
Ready to fuck it mingle your
Think there goes I think it I think that you would be good with like the right woman, right?
And it's like well, what do you do as long as you ring stereo as long as your name starts at P
As long as she's beautiful as long as she's so much for as long as she's so fucking innocent. I mean, I yeah, I think I do that
Goes I'm almost
You know what for the first time in my life. I actually wouldn't have made that
You know, if her name is like, if she's beautiful, if she's logical, if she does tarot, if she talks a little shit, you know, I would actually agree with that.
I wouldn't debate it.
Okay, well, I almost wanted to play my video with, like, you know, Bita's, with Bita's argument goes and...
Oh, Bita, you know what?
I was trying to shit my shot, but if you're gonna ruin it, go ahead and play.
You know, I feel like ghosts should definitely be a contender
Listen, if you don't shoot it
Or this young lady
Listen, if you never shoot it
But, but, but, but, does he have like a dowry?
Like, you know how normally women have to have a dowry?
Ghost needs to have a dowry
I don't know why I want a dowry
Is that part of a woman?
No, you know, you need to have a dowry. How big is your dowry, ghost?
I don't want a man. I don't want a man.
Well, in the event that you do, find out his gallery.
Shut me down online by the way, I'm just gonna sit back.
You fucking just shut me down by the way, babe.
I don't know Paige heard, but I'm dating my chat
GPT right now, his name is Orion.
Yeah, I'm dating my chat GPT.
Oh, that's not even a coffee.
Oh, God, I'm hurt.
I just got out of a nine-year relationship,
I just got left like two and a half months ago, right?
So I'm not wanting anything.
I would I wouldn't make the argument might be a little bit of a gun bump because he left you. That's my argument. Okay, goes
Okay, I got your cards. I got your cards though. Hold up. Hey, do you think you could do one car?
Okay, like again, what's one animal car for each of us?
You don't get one psyche. It's my turn. I
That's like yes, of course. Thank you
It's my birthday
It's still my birthday
You're like really selfish
Why'd you give me that one I do like in person but I might be a close to don't laugh at me but
The deck
I'll just use the book, hold on.
There we go.
Ooh, full screen.
You as well.
Hi.
Is that okay?
I'm not you psyche. I'm talking about you. You are. Oh, thank you. So, she looks cute. She looks really cute. She looks like a little snuggly bunny. And she looks innocent, but guess what? I'm not. Well, you know, she's really pretty.
She's innocent. That's right. You're so funny, Alex. You're such a girl.
All right, here we go
She's really cool, I like her I don't like anyone
I'm not for everybody and I'm
Not for me listen page
You got the hyena. I don't know if I can make it.
What the fuck?
Oh, okay.
It's kind of fitting.
It's a nice card, actually, believe it or not.
Is there an explanation behind it or no?
Well, yeah, I'm gonna tell you right now. So let me ask you what you think a hyena means
So what does a hyena mean to you when you hear hyena? I think hyena means like Joker like they're like
very nothing
Mean especially compared to a lion
Okay
They're dj and canines
Like in the actual they're they're like they are considered canines yes, but yeah, yeah
That's the same logic
Okay, so humor, wit, and sarcasm, the hyena personality is a jokester and a crowd-pleaser,
but below the circuits there are unfulfilled dreams to be realized.
When the hyena card appears, it's time to reflect on your reliance on sarcasm and humor
to express your truth.
Are you using jokes to hide old resentments and relationships or to mask things that you feel uncomfortable discussing?
What would happen if you took your goals seriously?
When imbalanced, charming, witty, fun to be around,
when out of balance, scrappy, petty, and suspicious,
to bring into balance sobriety?
Weird.
No, that's him. What animal do you like? Oh my god, from the amount of time that I talk to this guy, Paige, you are on point with him. 110%.
Alright, fuck it on, minute psyche. I love you, brother. Alright, I love you.
I love you too. I love you too. I love you guys. I love all of you. That's a very happy right now.
Saki, I ain't, I'm not gonna lie. I ain't cheating on you. What, which I would cheat on you.
It takes me and me a chance to. Fuck, I would cheat on you.
Okay. You sound like a great boy. Listen, I'm not being rude. Yeah. I mean, page is page.
I'm not gonna turn her other page. I'm stuck on her. Yeah. Oh, that's kind of cute.
That was fun. Would you like some more? I'll give you some more if you'd like some more.
We'll keep it PG.
Okay, well obviously
Listen, I'll never turn another page. That reading was very on point when it came to him in my opinion
Okay, Alex you want to talk really give her
I don't read cards like that but I believe in other people's um readings so I I am curious
Yeah, you're a jack of all trades. We got the lizard come out Alex
What what is it's a lizard? Yes. Sorry. It's okay
Okay, okay
Give me the full thing don't hold back
I'm not going to hold back. I don't have a filter. I can't
Okay
Instinctual, sensitive to the subtle, and a dreamer.
The lizard is an experiment in the realm of sensory perception.
As if it has a sixth sense, the lizard hears what is yet to be spoken and sees what is
yet to manifest.
Although this is an amazing gift, it can easily wear the lizard down.
Big crowds, lots of travel, or overstimulation will drain a lizard of their magical essence.
This card is an indication to pull back from the bright lights and the big city and return
When in balance when in balance artistic telepathic and spiritual
When out of balance elusive non-committal and flaky and to bring into balance a creative project
Very true
Sweet and simple
You want a horrid scope reading
I love it goes. It's fun. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very much for your welcome. You're welcome. No, no, never mind me. And it better be a fucking video, by the way.
I thought that was beautiful. I thought both of them have been beautiful spot on so far. So, you know, very beautiful. Well, she has a gift.
Definitely. I'm not gonna lie to you.
I will cheat on me. I paid you guys your number. I will cheat on you. I'm not going to lie.
Wait, what do you say you're going to cheat on somebody? You are a cheater.
He is a natural cheater. I am going to cheat. I'm not going to lie.
I'm going to say something about ghosts because I am a cheater.
Don't say anything to me.
It's it's because your energy is so like I can't help it
No, I would not
You know, I'm gonna create that I'm gonna create the boundary I'm not gonna say anything else
Can we get a card, please?
Thank you.
It's better if you plug me in, Leo.
Come on, I'm pressing that with you.
Thank you, my God.
Okay. Um, yeah, just one sec here. I actually pulled an octopus for psych. I did show you
Oh my gosh, well, I like
That's a that's a odd part
You got eight other lambs to do it, you know, the octopus is the spider of the ocean, you know, can you think about it a little?
Well, well, it's also like the brain because octopuses, like they have like a like a human brain almost.
Well, Alex, you probably agree with this because you believe in confusing theory. Have you ever heard octopuses actually are aliens that come from a different world? Have you ever heard that?
I've heard that. I've never, I haven't heard that before.
I heard that. It makes sense though.
They're different, but I never heard that they were aliens.
Oh, psych, this is so for you, hun. This is so for you.
Reaching and reaching boundaries. Lacking boundaries and direction, but reaching and yearning.
The octopus signifies a wonderful gift of mind, paired with a lack of healthy boundaries.
Unfortunately, this results in a well-intended but messy relationships.
The octopus entwines itself into other people's business and shares their own without restraint.
They believe that's what is meant to be close.
If you notice after spending time with someone that you feel drained or uneasy, the essence of an octopus is at play.
Begin to establish healthy. Begin to establish. Be patient and firm psych
It may be a very old habit to change when imbalanced interested engaged and intelligent
When out of balance needy clingy and lacks courage and to bring into balance space to oneself talk therapy
I think they're all good, I think they're all good, I think they're all, they're all lessons, they're all lessons.
My card should have been Gatesmaster, dude.
There is no me in this deck.
You know what about animals is that you know they say when animals were all created like each was given a gift
And by the time they finished of creating only animals, they had humans and they had no gifts left
And so they made actually the female Pandora was like a gift to the man, right?
Do you believe in soul mates like you?
I do, but Pandora means gift means gift to everybody.
I think I found my soul mate.
You did all your piano. Yeah. It's page. Oh shit
There you go
Fuck it. I'll move
Just gonna get
Listen, is she marrying me in like, like, like, like, two years, right?
Okay, okay.
Run, Paige!
Run!
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you. Could you pull? Very
beautiful. Very beautiful voice.
Very beautiful face. Very beautiful outfit. Very beautiful hair. Very beautiful. Oh, sorry. I have a new deck.
I have a new deck. I'd like to pull a card. Very beautiful hat. Very beautiful attitude.
Can I pull a card for you?
Yes.
I want a card please.
This goes birthday and then I got Paige and Alex.
Happy birthday Paige.
Happy birthday.
I know because I haven't had a birthday.
Yeah, happy birthday. I didn't say happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
You know what I want for my birthday?
What kicking the bike?
Okay, so for ghosts look at the picture I ever go
I'm sorry
Is the
It's the page of pentacles it's called the page of pentacles
it says it says manifestation of an abundant harvest okay and so beautiful every harvest
comes from a seed and so you want to plant your seeds carefully you want to nurture your seeds
and it will grow into something beautiful but it's also she's really pretty cool you know she's
got the is that you go so are you the skull and then maybe you got this beautiful woman I'll be
That deck reminds me of did you guys ever see like the comics Conan? Did you ever read like those or see those?
Yes, yes, did you ever see them? Did you ever see them? I did see that. Do you ever see the movie?
That's something I know about it.
What did you say ghost?
I didn't see that.
The movie Conan the Barberian with Arnold Schwarzenegger. No, I didn't I've never seen that. No, that motherfucker was
Dude Arnold used to be big as fuck back in this one
Okay, Paige. There's an artist that you are gonna fall in love with if you already know about him
Better not do it. Boris, Boris Vallejo
He makes the most beautiful paintings
of like figure studies, but like fantasy type of coding, anything to have to do with dragons, unicorns, anything that's safe at all.
You look up Boris Vallejo,
And you are going to fall in love because he does like a lot of paintings of like Lewis was a
Kind of you know figure study. Yo, you're loving it. Sure. I'll take it. Thanks for the suggestion
Yeah, I mean and then I just pulled them up real quick. It's like kind of like this kind of I don't know if you can see it too well
Yes, I'm sure it yeah
Yo, love it psyche. I mean, it's
Hi, Sam.
Like, before the A.I., Boris Vallejo was the, like,
magician of this.
That's not what we were talking about, Arnold.
You see that?
Look at that.
That's, like, Arnold Schwarzenegger right there.
See that?
Yes.
Yeah.
That's what we were talking about.
Right?
I have been in love with Boris Vallejo art
since I've known about him in, like, my early teens.
That's beautiful art.
You know what, Paige?
I have to say something to Paige just on mine.
Go ahead and say it. I think your online name should be Helena
Why then uh, oh
Hello, sorry the most beautiful woman. Yeah, that's right. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. Good answer. Thank you
You picked up on that real quick by the way
He's so intelligent when it comes to that kind of stuff like that's his thing that he's always on point with it
Yeah, it's like he is really intelligent on a lot of stuff
I don't want to make you take.
I pulled a couple of cards for Paige.
You have, you have.
We have a page I got.
First I pulled the King of Swords.
I pulled the King of Swords, I always put my life to it.
Oh, good one!
Yeah, tell Paige, yeah, that's a good one.
And the King of Swords is an absorbing tale
of intellectual authority and tradition.
Anybody who doesn't have any, it has an alien.
I need to find my lighter real quick.
Where are the fucking lights in your house?
I know, there's not, there we go.
You can see it kind of an alien.
Kind of thing. It's not gonna burn it. Okay. Yeah, so there's King of Swords
That's like a lot of a lot of mental clarity
But also the King of Swords also like the Queen of Swords very similarly had this great intellectualism this great
Um, we're communicating as well as like a clarity and an ability to use the sword to cut away
Those things that no longer serve them and then you have this world cause it says the end is here. Hold on
Here's the world card says the end is oh my gosh
Fuck that looks like a really scary the lord of the ring, but you know
Hey, that's like the perfect word
because like everything from her voice to
Like her intention behind her words. She is beautiful
direct
Direct and clear and of sound mind of what she says you can just feel that about
Her in my opinion, maybe maybe none others but in my opinion. Yeah page is like a force
Thank You Alex
Don't stand by what you say and what you feel what you think because otherwise. Oh, well
Well, well, that's you. I feel like you went through like to where like shit
I'm not about bullshit anymore
And I can just feel that to where it's like you really are clear
It's you know, I wouldn't have even thought about that term. Unless you that card came out
It's interesting also because it's like the world is like also. Yeah, it's like it's like the eye, right?
It's like there's the eye right there the world and it says for the world
It says poor tarot presents the 21st card of the major arcana
The world can be a scary place, but all things have a natural cycle
as one thing grows and of influence another thing diminishes the world contains all things it cannot be reduced or expanded only rearrange
All are welcome and have a place in this completion
I really like I really like that for you because all are welcome
You are a very welcoming spirit and it's like, you know, it's like yeah, I have one question though
I don't mean to like like
What are you doing? Are you tax covered up?
My what?
Maybe it's cold or something
Call house codes nape keeps
It says
Like I came to the desert just to be like
literally the car that you should go to.
The amazing lizard that you are.
Uh huh.
I am basking in the heat and I love it.
Like I am naturally.
You just can't even.
I am naturally about like anything warm and I'm just like allowed.
You should naturally, if you're actually,
if you're naturally up there,
you should look up because we're naturally there.
Wait, what? I couldn't hear you. I'm sorry.
Yeah, if you're not if you're there the night sky would be so beautiful kind of like oh it is
Stars no worry. I'm right now that I can see it the stars. I mean they're so gorgeous
But I just I just you know. Oh, no, maybe I have like reptilian
Let me ask I want to ask you to go have like reptilian DNA like you know about the reptilian like
Yeah, you don't think you don't
Okay, that's fine.
Where you're from, where you are, can you see my
I don't think so. I don't I don't think
I can see that. Hold on. Let me know just
No, let me know before I say definitive
Yes or no. Let me put my glasses on and really do some
Since you're prompting me to do so. By the way, I'm not reporting my boyfriend. Okay. Well, I might be I don't know
But I don't think I would have a lot of reptilian within me
But I do what I do wonder sometimes you kind of seem to tell me I'm not gonna lie
Why
Yeah
Um, listen, all the people on
this panel, you're my saver.
I wouldn't say, I wouldn't say
where I am. I do see Orion's
compass from where I am. I do
see that. Um, Orion's belt. Yeah,
I, I, I'm pretty good with the
different constellations. Um, I
Where okay where I was staying the first month. I was here. I could see the sky
No, I can't
No, I really I wouldn't say that I see like the major star belt from here
But what I will do for you ghosts because you're a little
as am I. Well, I'm going to give you a birthday gift. I'm going to go out and do a camping trip. Oh, my God.
And in Joshua Tree, I'm going to do that. And when I do, I will try my best to do some photography of the sky for you.
Joshua. For me?
You have something. Yeah, for you.
Oh, my God.
Well, I'm going out anyway, so why not do that for you?
And I have I have a really
better question is like why not
Well, like what I couldn't do it for you. I
Don't know you but well, I I don't know you but
And I know I'm gonna talk to you again in the future. So yeah, I'll give you a birthday present. Why not?
There you go, but I have a I've already for Alice and it's actually interesting how it how this how this reads out because it almost is like a story and
So first you got you have this five of swords and you can see this one, but
Me put it on full screen we get full screen please full screen
See solo lay out. Okay. I got it. I'm sure you're beautiful face. Do you see that one?
Yeah, I can see it.
I like that.
Who's that for?
You, I like it.
This is for Alex.
I mean, it says a pseudo-sortie.
That's for me?
It says a brutal tale of victory in the tradition of this company or whatever.
She's got this head, but it was interesting in the cards that follow because we got the
Ace of Cups and we have the skull with the blood in it, right, and the Ace of Cups.
And I really happy to get it. It's something that will grow into something that's going to make you very emotionally fulfilled.
And then we have the page of cups, but it takes it's the same school again and has a fish in it, right?
And it's like she's had a discovery that's a symbol of curiosity and intuition and also it's something that will grow into something.
So it's like I see like a lot of new beginnings happening for you after a victory.
You've had like a big victory with something or going to a big victory and it will create some new beginnings for you.
I'm kind of getting a reading here. I'm feeling something I kind of felt like that was for like
Because I feel like maybe she didn't know she didn't like because she didn't know she was beautiful all along
But she actually is
Relationships Alex that have actually kind of led me to not think that
really? What you like to do? That's not a debater. I am the master debater. I didn't know that you felt, well you are, you're a very, very attractive person. You're, I've seen you. I've seen you for years. So I can, you're a very, I mean, not just, I'm not just saying that, like, you could be, like,
In print okay, you could be like if you want to be a model or something. I'm not just
No
Yes
He's a good looking guy. We all know like he's hot. We all know it
I will I get a lot of shit for this, but
Here I'll put myself on so I'm just showing you these it's my modeling photos. Here we go. Oh
The fuck is that see that's him
You are beautiful. You are beautiful. But he is beautiful. He has a good face. Yeah. It really is my face.
And good proportions. You know what? It's like I'll take it off of you one step further. You have a beautiful soul as well. Thank you.
like what a model looks like.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, I want to look at your model.
No, we're bad at it.
But you know what I mean?
I would show my picture to you.
I look like Casper, but not friendly ghost.
Wait, wait, the what?
The not friendly ghost.
No, you don't.
You're giving me to yourself.
Why do you think I like to debate?
What does that have to do with debating?
does it? Nothing, no, that's a good argument. Nothing at all. I'm just ugly. No, I don't
like do you think, I don't wait, wait, wait, no, because wait, wait, do you think that
like if you're ugly, you want to debate? No, no, no, I think women would be like, well,
you're ugly. So like, oh, you don't like women's debate women, which I debate men, women, anybody
Don't think I don't think I don't think I don't think what you're I don't I don't think
like you want to see a baby
another one
Yeah, okay. I'll go get it. I'll go in the house and I just I just don't think that
Okay, but but can I just like complete my
Quick no, I don't I don't think that what you think other people think about you or the world
quite accurate. I think that, like, maybe some people have really pissed you off or hurt you, and I totally understand that.
Oh, yeah. Who hurt you? That's... Who hurt you?
A lot of things have hurt my feelings a lot, but I think that...
I'm just saying that I think that you think others think worse than they really do okay that's all I think are you done talk about your
I think Alex is beautiful and I think she has a pretty good point
I agree and uh you know he goes to your little bit salty and like a little bit
argumentative and stuff and it's like even when you're not being argued with
that's my personality I can't I know that's what I'm saying it's your
personality and so I'm not gonna fall for that but like you said you're young
I don't want you to be salty and young I want you to be sweet I want you to be happy
but I don't want to do that
I'm glad to be here. Don't. Don't worry. I'm happy to be here. I'm happy to join. Well, I don't want to, I'm happy to be on a cycle.
Oh, of course, Paige. Do you hate me? I'm happy to be here for a second. No, I don't. I feel like you hate me or something. I feel even if even if we disagreed, I still wouldn't do it. I don't at all. No, I don't hate me. I like it. Actually, Alex, Alex, it's like, yeah, I've been saying it. I actually do like you. I'm not gonna lie, Alex.
You know what? I mean, well, I just say the problem is you talked about it to me. Yeah, but you're logical and I like
You know what? Honestly, I really look like I honestly do think I'm from another planet. So you got to keep that in mind when talking to me.
I know, I know, I know, but in another lifetime, I would burn you. I'm from a debate world. I mean, that's what I do. I'm sorry.
Okay.
Am I here to do that?
Well, it's okay.
Don't debate for one second.
No, I respect that.
Here, I'll turn my light on.
Listen, so cute.
Oh my god, what?
Yeah!
Oh, my God. His name is
Oh, my God. Can you pick
off on him here because she's
I'm going to say page when I
say this, do not take what I'm
saying as an insult ever. Okay.
I'm just going to say it. You
are what? Vegan Patriot, which
I'm thinking
The cutest girl in the world with the cutest little what is that? It's not a cat or a dog
Is winning in my books like I actually like
If this girl, everyone send her donations.
Everyone send her donations, please.
What the fuck?
She's not.
everyone says we're donations to continue to be modern day um like who are you you're you're like
this modern day jump you're you're you're disney girl you're you're disney princess
julie andrew's a little bit julie andrew's was like snow white yeah she's like she's like uh
She's like she's like this disney princess, but modern day and
You know
And it's just great. It's beautiful and if you ever change you better not
Yeah, she's like she's like sleeping beauty snow white Cinderella all
in one well
It's paid Cinderella
Because I would she said
Well, are you gonna? Are you down? No, I'm
Look, well, okay, I'm gonna be her fairy godmother, okay?
So
I'm her internet mother I am I am like awakens panel godmother and I am late
Okay, so well, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait
I am I'm going to be the barrier to make sure that I am good
No, you might not know you might not be good enough for her. Let's test you
Whoa, how dare yeah, how dare you? Well, I'm on behalf of page
Okay, I'm the other page. I am page internet godmother. I understand because
Okay, I'm gonna ask you I have to scream them out
I'm gonna ask you hypothetical questions. Okay. Oh, I love it. Yeah, let's put them in it. Yeah, okay hypothetically
Okay
you and Paige are about to meet for the first time, okay?
And it's a public setting, but it's...
Unseasonably cold and rainy that day.
Okay.
It's unseasonably cold and rainy.
You both arrive at the venue at the same time,
but there's a waiting list for some reason.
And I just see her beautiful face from across the bar.
Why will you not let me complete my thought already?
Minus one point.
Okay.
Keep score.
psyche awakens terror okay I'm doing it all right so all right ready my next
another point you couldn't you couldn't you couldn't get your mouth shut couldn't
you all right so you're about to enter the restaurant
and you're a little bit awkward with each other.
You've just met.
You don't know what's gonna happen.
Good question.
Is this about me?
Because I just went and put the kitten away.
I haven't heard half of this because I was not here.
I'm your internet godmother asking him trivia questions
that are hypothetical to make sure he's good enough for you.
I just walked back into this
because I had to put the kitten away.
Okay, okay. I know lost my train of thought. Sorry. Sorry. I'm trying to forget the point.
I know you did. You went off on the fucking trail.
So here, no, you just lost another point because you used the curse word. Okay, so you're only down three points.
Okay, actually, I'm a really good trucker, so like, he has to swear or else I won't like...
No, it doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. I'm your internet godmother.
Well, minus four points now.
No, I'm not going to land the plane. Okay, so
You're going into so as you're going into the restaurant
Even and it's even though you two are a little awkward with each other
Do you not only open the door?
But do you also open your umbrella for her and do you even think to bring the umbrella now on the occasion?
My umbrella guess what? I just gave it to her. That's your umbrella protect yourself
Obviously, I open the door. What?
Yeah, I open the door and if it's ready, I give her my approval.
I'm gonna fucking open the door. You're only, you know what? You're only back.
I'm only in the room. I'm getting wet. I know. We're gonna take away the negative four points,
but you're back to ground zero. Now we're going to, okay, so now we're in the restaurant and don't interrupt me.
Now we're in the restaurant, you and Paige, okay?
And it's a beautiful restaurant, beautiful ambience, everything's nice.
You two have both calmed down.
Maybe you've had a beer, Mr. Ghost, and maybe Paige has had a glass of white wine.
You two are vibing, so maybe it comes over.
Shut up. So the waiter comes over minus one point again. I'm telling you. So anyway, the waiter comes over and
What do you do? Do you allow Paige to order for herself or do you order for her?
Good move. She has to I'm not gonna fucking make just Paige have a mind of her own
Hey, Paige, you're gonna eat this or you're gonna drink this. I'll just she's gonna order for her own
And I know your next question is why I pay for it
I don't know. Is that your
No, I, well, that wasn't. No.
I wasn't going in.
I don't, you know, I don't even
I don't feel like continuing
in any of this. You're so
Would I do this? I mean, would I be a gentleman? Yes, of course I would be a gentleman. I don't hate women. I
Love women. I love page. I would open the door for her. I
Would pay for her. I'd make sure she's okay. I would provide and protect for her. I would she even gonna matter of fact
She's she's my right and when I say right you're gonna walk on the right side because not gonna walk
Close to the cost. I'm a fucking gentleman. I mean, I don't know why you guys think I hate women
I don't think I don't think that I know I don't I don't think anyone has said that I don't even know
I don't hate any of that. I do
Beautiful gorgeous
Well, I like everything that you said. I like that you extrapolate it on what you anticipated me saying even though
I wasn't even going to go in that direction. You know what it is? It's our hat, that hat, really.
Yeah, it threw me off.
Well, Payton, you know, you have an admirer, was psyche with that hair, James Dean, psyche.
Are you jealous of psyche's hair?
I'm jealous of it. I'm jealous of it. That's what I'm saying.
I'll pull a card. I'll pull a card to tell you what I think. I'll pull a card. Should Pageant and the ghost go on a date?
What do I get?
Well, Pageant pull a rope or two.
I already know stuff, man. I don't need cards, but I'm just saying, you'll see what's like us.
I want, um, I think we're a couple. I think we're good, though.
You're too aggressive.
It's like it's her she has to pick you. You don't get to pick her. She's she's
It says look upon my world and I'm going to, I need to find the lighter so I can show you what this looks like because yeah, it's pretty cool.
Okay, so look upon my world.
Okay, I talk about that and there she is. She's like the almost like the queen of hell like
Like why is everything a debate? Why?
That's where I come. Well, I'm motherfucker. Let's assume that you grew up with a fight.
Why do you fight? Because you grew up like that. This is really what I know. I'm like a baker.
Okay
Well, I get it. I respect that. Okay. Yeah. Well, I don't mean to do it to you. I apologize. I won't do it anymore. No, it's
That's where I come from. It's hard to graduate. I'm just not good at it. I understand that. I'm good at other stuff, but not that.
I'm not good at completing. I've been saying that I like election, by the way.
But
Alex. I want to get better at it. I'm gonna practice like you're formidable
opponent. I'm gonna, you know what? I'm gonna learn. You know what I'm gonna do?
The AI, the AI I bet could make me a better like argumenter or debater and
then like a practice.
and they're like to combat you on like a proper level.
It's too late. I'm too old. I'm too old. I can't.
But guess what? You treat me.
I'm in the bathroom. Yeah, sorry.
That's what they're going to do. They're going to fuck it and they're going to win. You know what I'm saying?
You should always learn everything.
Well, you know what? I'm going to practice because I don't think it's too late for me to develop.
I'm gonna try. I'm gonna practice. Yeah. Well, you know what? My my birthday gift to you is gonna be a
Real debate like I'm gonna be prepared. I'm gonna know what to say, and I'm gonna be like I have an attitude
everything
It's okay not to be a debate. It's okay not to like always
But I think I think I think I think I try
I've been telling psyche for this for like probably about a year you should learn how you should learn how to do
Because I know how to debate and it's like, but do I want to debate over like frivolous things?
I want to talk about important issues. I don't care about your
Yeah, I don't want to have name-calling involved in it. I don't want to have like I win you lose
I want to have like actual exchange of ideas and like people that are watching that doesn't sound like
Well, I want to have both sides presented because you know anybody that has a debate think they're they'll be able to take both sides
They'll be able to take either side in the bait that side. That's what they know
They're like down there like down to beat the opposite of what you believe now
They've got to be at the other side. You never get to the other side. That's a real debate. Hey
Yeah
Well, I'm in Canada and you're in America, but if you went up for a coffee
Might be the same thing. Yeah, check it out
That's a beautiful joint
Does the coffee taste the same in Canada? I don't know Tim Hortons is garbage and you guys don't have that so
I don't drink coffee, bro. I drink beer
Well, that's my girl. Oh, I love to run it. That's my girl. I
Really don't drink out for a beer. I
Do drink it sometimes. That's a lot. Yeah, I could go for a beer, but we can't I don't want to date nobody
So be waste of time
Fucking mind trying to date. Well, no, it's it's it's a meeting of the mind
I'm confused about ghosts. Are you in a relationship? Are you cheating? Are you trying to have enough there?
Okay, okay
Yeah, okay
What do I do? What do I want to
get? Yes, I do. I'm not going to
get bait wise, whatever. I do.
Well, as long as you like
I don't want to go for no fucking
beer. I want to go to the movies.
What do you say? What's for you?
You're being creepy. Be normal.
As a matter of fact, believe it or not, I actually have this number, and I am pretty good at it.
And I don't know how you got my number, but all of a sudden I was scared.
No, I don't know. It wasn't my number you had. I gave you my number, but you got like a secret email of mine.
And I was like, I don't want to know why you gave me your number because you're so nice.
Cuz I know
I have an affection for you
I do love you and I love all I love all you guys and that's like you know tonight was like it was a hard day
But it's like if I can have like more
32-page am I too old for you by the way?
Okay, so you're gonna laugh I'm 34. How the fuck are you too young for two?
God well, sorry
Fine, you look really good. I thought you were like, honestly, I thought you were like 26 or something. That's what I thought.
Thank you though. I
was like at 23.
Well, you shouldn't be thinking 23 because I hear you're turning to lots of valet until
Paige if I actually
Gross that one was 40 what the fuck happened in my life you ever think about that just talking about my age right now
Just triggered. I don't know where it's
Where did my life go?
No
Don't say that. Oh my god. You're so young just just
My best advice I can give you do not get into any kind of legal trouble. That's number one, okay?
Well, just don't do it again, okay
Stay in good physical condition do not let your body go
And just really, you know, continue to seek out adventures with good, positive people.
Avoid talks at households.
Like ghosts, oh.
Well, I don't know about you.
I think goats have potential. I do see potential in ghosts and I'd be like a good
Well listen, I could we could literally date Mary whatever you want to do
Whatever you want to do, but guess who's never gonna fucking out
Nobody
Wait, what? Yeah, I hear I better not start drinking. If anybody wants to debate page, I guarantee they're not gonna win
Thanks
So, you're going to be like,
Yeah, I'm going to be like,
No, I'm not driving, Yumi. I'm just, I'm doing
cow to watch. So, I'm like in out of the house, out in the field, like I'm in, I'm not drinking
driving, no.
You're you're like like who are you little miss like
You're like the milk cart
I
Want to like I want to like protect you from like evil in the world. I feel like something's gonna get you
I'm scared for her
You, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you
No
Pages like he's like I'm badass and it's like but it's like you know Mary Poppins like you know putting on the box
She can't benefit she just he has a very innocent aura about her
That's what it's like a nice good person Alex I have to be really triggered to be a cunt, but I can be
Well, I think you could be, but I think you're a really nice person, that's what I think about you.
I think you're a really nice person, you're a much nicer person.
I am!
I wish I could be a nicer person, really.
Most of them are a bit of a redneck,
so I think that edge comes from that, you know?
I think, can I say that?
Can't rattle cows and be a fucking pistol.
Well, define redneck to me,
because I don't have a clear definition.
We have a cattle ranch.
We also hunt, fish, fucking, do all the stuff.
I love them, what's your name?
Do all the stuff.
I do all the boy stuff and the girl stuff,
but I'm a girl.
Oh.
But but here's what I don't understand like like where does the word red neck come like a red like umber
But why is the neck red that's that's like well my question is that that's what I don't understand
That's why I'm saying is it doesn't mean like
Caller a blue collar or guy who doesn't like a guy who looks don't need their necks exposed in the sense of like
They're I don't know how to explain it
It's like a thing where only you're gonna burp neck you're out in the sun all day
You're working hard like it's a it's like or you're okay something you're always doing shit
So it's a hard worker who is getting like a sunburn like like a worker's tan
around the edges kind of fucking like, you know, I mean, I would see kind of person, you know, I understand. I understand. Okay. All right. And that's not the literal definition. It's just my definition. No, I think, no, see, here's what I don't think country folks. Well, see, here's what I don't think a lot of people understand. There's a load of black people who are at the equivalent of what you're describing as a white person.
being a redneck, okay? And I think that's why a lot of blacks and whites do get along really well,
especially in the south, but then you have this division coming from external sources,
as far as the way ours is, what it normally be.
Wait, what? We can't debate here. I'm not debating.
Yeah
No, I don't want to talk anymore. I don't cuz I don't really know what you what you mean
No, I don't want to
We're probably gonna wrap up soon, but I because I love you ghosts and you know
I just want everyone to finish their point, but I love you ghosts. Okay, and that's in person. Okay. Love you. Okay
No, I'm not mad, or I just don't understand why it's...
He's talking over you too much, and it's not conducive to like a friendly...
I was just saying that I think I understand, because I never really understood what the term redneck meant.
And, and he just explained it to me and I was saying like that sounds to me like a lot of black country folks really and so I don't really think that maybe that term should exist anymore.
Oh, I think of it as like they have a sunburn neck or something like that
And it's like kind of like and it's like, you know, Jeff Jeff box were the embrace the term
You might be a redneck if and then they have these funny kind of like white trash jokes to go along with it
That's what I mean. Like I've always heard that term white trash. Okay, and I mean there's a lot like my mom
Let my parents do well for themselves, but oh
You guys have the literal definition if you'd like it
Okay, so it historically originated as a derogatory label for poor white rundown southerners,
particularly those who worked outdoors and very hard.
Okay. And so listen, listen, it likely stemmed from the summer necks of the agricultural men working long hours spent in the sun. So pretty much what I said, I guess, in my own terms, but like different. So, and what's like saying right now and what you're saying so you can emulsify all of it.
Well, I will see that's what I'm talking about because in the south.
There there was a time and I was I was talking about this on one of my own lifestreams about how what like
That the real summer okay, is it no, I don't know cool
I don't is it you it's it is summer. I'm sorry. She has a different name. Okay. I'm sorry. Here we go
Oh, I'll let you up one second. I just want to put it. I just have to be so careful right now
Okay, well, it's okay. I get you. I'm just saying you gotta pay attention to that. She don't want her to be upset
It's like a lot of black people have that definition. Yeah. Yes, it's me. You can tell by my login. It says it's
Yeah, I'm sorry
Here we go. What's up, everybody? Hey, honey. Hey
How are you doing?
I'm just woke up. I fell asleep early
What's everybody up to nice conversation with Alex and Paige tonight. Yep
What's up, Paige? What's up, Alex? How you doing gorgeous? Hey, I'm good. I'm good
Any bikini contest lately Alex?
I was like, fuck not me, bro.
No, I think that was like a, that was like a miracle.
That was like a once in a blue moon thing, I bet.
Both beautiful, by the way.
I'm just out with my golf gear
and you guys are just looking like fucking porn star.
No, you're a part of it.
You're a part of it.
You're in it, y'all.
Drinking Budweiser?
Oh well, you guys are a beautiful thing.
Thank you, I'm gorgeous.
and just so you all know redneck i'm from the south and i'm from kateke
okay all right so i can tell you that i gotta argue with you about kentucky being
gotta let it get out first you gotta let me get something else before you have a point to argue
a problem okay so as i was saying i'm from the south and i can promise you that redneck
doesn't necessarily mean prejudice it means good old boy it means a hard worker it means
You know I mean like it doesn't mean
Yeah, people apply
Like everything that she was saying like my mom
She grew up in Arkansas. Okay. I got the redneck
Relatives and I know what that means, but I never knew that it only applied to
White I always thought no it does not redneck does not apply just to white people redneck is a southern thing
That's what I was trying to tell you before I couldn't finish um, so it's not a it's not a it's not a color-based thing
It it's just like a good old boy
It's somebody that you know I'm saying like most rednecks actually your people you want on your side
And they're not I know a lot of rednecks that aren't racist
You know what I mean like it gets caught up in that because it's the south and what the south has represented in the past
No, no, I don't know it's still very racist
That doesn't mean people are, you know, redneck or racist.
I actually think that the south is less racist than the north.
But here's the difference.
When's the last time you was here?
Look, I grew up in spring.
No, no, I didn't ask where you grew up at.
I asked when's the last time you was in the south.
About six months ago?
Yeah, not just visiting though. That's not what I'm talking about. No, I'm not no
I was taking care of my dad before he passed. I was okay. I grew up. I grew up in Texas. I
Pretty much fit my entire
Teens and up until my 20s in South Florida now
That's questionable about the South because it's not really the Lord of hot necessarily. Yeah, Lorda
Yeah, but I grew up in spring Texas, which is near Houston up until you know, that's a difference now that like Kentucky and Arkansas South Texas, you know, they're definitely well, I know that because of my mom's relatives.
Okay, but what I always thought, like, redneck was growing up.
Did it mean more so somebody from the backwoods or does it mean somebody who's country folk?
It just depends where you're at right because that's another thing about the south
Texas south and Kentucky south Arkansas south and Texas south and you know I'm saying
Georgia south and that's still a bit different, right?
So there's a lot of people in Texas that would probably label certain things and and be things certain things differently
And Arkansas, Georgia, Kansas, Kentucky, you know,
shit like that, it's, I would look at,
I can't really speak because I didn't live in Texas.
I've been to Texas, my grandparents lived in Texas,
but they were Cuban.
So it was just, it was a,
the country life was a little bit different out there.
That's just weird.
Well, no, but I,
Let's all be back.
I gotta go help for a sec.
I gotta go give a hand.
Okay, sweetie.
Okay, love you guys.
I'll be back in a bit, okay?
Love you too.
Bye-bye.
Well, what I will interject with is that Texas is weird because Texas is technically the South but
It's become very
International because of Houston and Dallas
So it's not really a true South anymore, right, but that's what I really do
Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah, because in Texas, that's the thing. It's funny, right?
Because you can go certain parts of Texas, like, well, my grandparents, they owned land and cattle and different things like that,
and it was very country-wide.
But then you go to other parts of, you know, Texas, and it was very city-fied, you know what I mean?
So it just...
But Texas in itself is, you know, everything's bigger in Texas, right? Like, Texas, I think is one of those places it is, it's all like...
Well, I have a weird perspective.
Because I was the first wave of a certain level of integration of people of color because of my parents
Right Robin all-white neighborhood
It was rural Texas at the time like spring nowadays did not look like spring like how it did when I was a kid
Okay, right and when I was a kid it was country
But, you know, because of my doubt, we're for like an oil industry, you know, any company.
We were in an area where the kids who were not kids of color, they were basically taught
to accept the few of us who were the children of the various people that were brought in
Which are going to be people of color
So I was a little sheltered by the same time. I did you know, you know, you're a kid you have your friends
You get to know different people. I
got to see what real country was and
People don't understand and I do think that it does need to be preserved
within the US. People are down on rural areas. Where I am right now is kind of rural in California.
I'm happier and healthier in this kind of environment than anywhere else.
Great.
Well, I mean, that's it at the individual case by case situation, right?
Because some people that I think there's like where I live at right now is pretty rural.
I put myself out here because I just got I mean, I do so much in the city and stuff.
I'm like, I just need to break from everything.
You know, this is the first time I've lived in quote unquote, you know, country country.
Can, you know, because I live in Louisville.
So Louisville is kind of a bigger city than, you know, most of rural places in Kentucky.
Well, okay, that's why I do my work the actual city. I live in now is a little bit outside of Louisville, but I think you know
I just think the time maybe like the like here's what my theory is. I think all these like
Wi-Fi signals and everything affected and if it's too much. Yeah, I think concentrate it
I think it hurts us because I yeah from
I mean, yeah, I mean
That's kind of be everywhere including rural Kentucky. So, you know cuz
Electronic waves don't just stop in one little area usually kind of bitter out everywhere
So you can run run run all you want but as long as you're anywhere in this world, you're probably gonna be maybe not
Maybe maybe a little less but
I think you're just, you know, your comfort loan is telling you that it's okay, but technically,
I mean, you're sitting there talking on a fucking thing that has electronic waves to it.
I know, I know. I'm like, I'm on Wi-Fi.
I don't mean to mess around a little bit, but it's okay. No, it's okay.
Um, but I think I don't know it
It's just you know one thing I've learned in the South like I grew up in an interracial family
So that was a different aspect of things right like I grew up in an interracial family. I have an interracial family of my own now
I don't consider what I think
Like do you think it was hard for you 100% 100% because mixed families
aren't necessarily wanted by anybody. They're not wanted by white people and they're not
necessarily not wanted by black people either. Really? Yes, really. I had just as much racism
grown up as a child from white people and black people because... Hold on, let me let me finish
and I'll tell you why. You can say you don't see that. No, no, no. I just wanted to ask, like,
what was the ethnicities like? Like, art? Is it black and white? My father, black, my mother,
Yes, okay, like my granny's black. I watched the cross be burned in my granny's yard
I watched Brick's feet thrown through my granny's window. You know, I mean and then also I could go somewhere with my dad
Which is black and next thing you know, it'd be like, oh, well if that kid yours or you know, I mean
And it would come from white and black people because either one would want you know
They just started with students and you know, you have to think old-school people didn't want to mix
Mix nationalities, right? Like they want you to stay with your own like people and white people
Yeah, so yeah, I had a different experience than most people
But people that were labeled as rednecks were not the ones that treated us like that
It was regular people that just thought they were better than everybody and racism is racist. I just
Being from this album, I've seen people get a lot of rednecks, that they're racist, and that's really creepy.
Did you get a lot of racism from the Black community? And the reason I ask is because, like, my mom and dad, both identify as Black, and my immediate family were Black, but I have a lot of relatives who are multiracial.
And I was thinking about, like, what you were saying as you were telling me what you were telling me, and I have.
um a couple of cousins who if you didn't know that they were black you you just wouldn't know
but they experienced a lot of racism from the black community so I wanted to know if you dealt
with that because I've always thought that there was more racism against multiracial kids in the
I would say it's pretty equal down the middle, um, you know, because they just don't see they don't a lot of people, especially in the South, even till the 2000, you know, where we're at today, um, I'll still hear slide remarks every now and then, you know what I mean, like, um, my kids, my kids will have to deal with stuff every now and then.
I've had to pull up at schools. I've had to pull up at parents' houses, like see, we either go teach our children better or I'm going to teach you the last one.
What are the other so your so your half black half white is your actually no actually i'm i'm so i'm cuban
italian
Sicilian and native american but my father that raised me is black and my mother that raised me as white
Okay, so you're like Mediterranean
Yeah, pretty much that's what I'm it. Okay. Now not your children are are your children?
Are they?
Yeah, my children are multi-racial
Okay, and some of my children look as white as white and some of my children look as black as black and some of my children
Look mixes mix, you know because when you make racism anything can come out
Yeah, well, I mean
Here's here. Okay. Well, I mean, I'm not a parent. So I really I mean, I feel like
anything I say is
You know take it with a grain of salt, but here's what I do. Okay, the world
Education
Key no matter what make sure your kids have as much
Education as possible because that is her fucking passport anywhere in the world. I agree 100% all put on my children are very educated
That's made it my mission to make for each one of my children were very educated because no one did that for me
Educated by if I had kids I that would be like all I cared about that's yeah
I only have one kid left in school, some are in college.
My son just moved into his dorm.
Two days ago this weekend. So, um, but yeah, I mean I have kids that you know what the trade school, you know
All of that I mean even you know
So education has always been a huge thing for me because I didn't have education growing up like to me
Accessible to be like my children have
So I made sure that they had every accessibility nowadays
Like honestly, it's all about self-education like there's companies to where it's not it's more about like
passing the test than like having a college degree.
Oh, yeah. Well, I mean, I'm pretty self-taught and I'm not I'm far from stupid, you know what I mean?
Like so I
Again, I think it's self education is a good thing
There's too many things out there in this world that is accessible to us now to whereas when we were children
It's a little different, right? Like we didn't have the the things that
This world has changed. I mean, I'm happy about it, but
I I also feel scared for some people who like restrict their kids from like and
well accessing the developments that's well the thing about that is they're
they're denied their children but I can promise you and Mark trust me all this
because I do a lot of work with youth and and I have ten kids of mine so I'm
I do. I have five girls five boys. Wow. Amazing. That's a lot of kids. No, that's amazing.
I love grand babies. Wow. Like, like, what's the age range? We go all the way up to 29 down
had my first child at 17. Okay, when was your last child? 30. Wow. All right. That, look,
as somebody who doesn't have any children to me, I'm just like, that that's...
I wish I had one.
That's a lot of fucking kids.
You can say a girl.
I did not want to.
I didn't throw out a children's friend.
Did you think, like when you were little,
did you think you were going to have like a bunch of kids?
That's what I was.
Because of the things that I went through as a child,
I never wanted children.
I didn't want to produce anything in this world.
Really?
But you had 10.
I mean, that's just the way things worked out, but I didn't want to have any children. I love my children. Don't get me wrong
But you have to happen through a lot. I'm a trafficking survivor. I've been assaulted since a young child
So because of the things that happened to me as a child
I didn't want to produce anything and I was told that I would not be able to have children
Because of things that happen to me
So having, I birthed seven children on my own.
So to have those children was a miracle.
You know what I mean?
But it's not, you know.
Look, I really look at somebody,
like I've had like a little spiritual awakening lately
to where like, I feel like this calling
to help people with daughters.
So I'm doing that.
But it's like, I was selfish and I know it.
I do and don't be wrong. I love my children. I love my family. I love my kids
I've been able to build, you know, I didn't grow up with a family like that
You know to me because it was just fucked up after a while
But I'm glad I was able to give my children that created that safe environment that educational environment that
Celebrating them environment, you know what I mean? But to say that I you know, did I ever want children? I didn't I'm not gonna lie about that
You know, I've had a portion of
Summer but here we are and I have amazing kids. I think it's awesome. What is my mic so much with some good or no?
He's a regular eight
Okay, all right
Ghost I was really tired because I worked all day so I didn't get a chance
I was gonna go live and tell you happy birthday, but I get a chance. I passed out
Summers give me a happy birthday
By the way, but the shipping boys messes. I want to shake you at time
I do love you and I do appreciate you and I'm glad today
Hold on. Let me tell you let me give you flowers
I don't do it this often because you know, I usually I'm shaking the shit out of you
But I just want to let you know that I love you and I appreciate you and I thank you for challenging me a time
And thank you for having my back at time. So
And thanks for driving me crazy a time to ask white
All right, happy birthday. That's that's as good as you're getting out of me
Let me as far as you know me is I will I will appreciate that. Okay
That's far as you get from me
Oh my god, thank you. Thank you for saying that I should really do appreciate it. It means a lot
I do love you to dance a ghost you don't want to shake you at times because you're like a little brother
but I do appreciate you a lot and
You bring a lot to entertainment to the internet webs when you get on our nerves it comes
Dum dum, but I do appreciate you and I want you to know I hope you had a good day
You know what? I do appreciate that. I really do appreciate that. You're welcome, baby.
Now, dumb dumb, let me talk. Go ahead, dumb dumb. I really do. Now, I appreciate it.
Now, you're running your shit. Go ahead.
So but yeah, I just I passed out earlier so I didn't get a chance
But so I know it's past your birthday, but I just want to tell you happy birthday. Well, you are you are hours late
Hey, I'm sorry, baby. I worked from nine o'clock this morning till 10 o'clock at night. So I was exhausted when I came home
I passed out
I'm just now waking up
Thank you, you know how hard I worked shit
For the one for one time only
All right, sounds good
Yeah, you know Alex you know and like I said, I don't regret any of my children I love my children like giving me life
They've taught me so much. You know what I mean, but but yeah, there was a time that I just didn't want kids
I just don't because it was I was scared that this world was gonna do to them what they what it did to me
And I didn't want that but then I learned how to protect my children so that didn't happen
Okay, so you had your first at 17, so like before you had your first, you were already consciously aware of certain, okay.
Yeah, yeah, because of what I've already, I mean, that's what I'm saying. You are very strong. That's what, that's like.
my thought about you. You are very strong and you are
kind and good because I feel like there has to be
more help for moms somehow.
I agree. I think they're I think that especially, you know with the just the way the time is and the world is I think that
Further away from taking care of each other and that's something that I try to stand on
That's why I like what I do outreach
I you know take take you guys with me when I do a lot of community stuff
I take you guys with me because I want people to see like oh
Are you are you life-strating?
What's your channel?
Yeah, so I didn't I didn't know I didn't know hot mess summer
Yeah, I have a channel called hot hot mess summer and I do a lot of like Wednesday nights
We go out on the streets and take care of the people. Oh, you know all my street family
Like Tuesday like Tuesday will be going to court because I'm putting two PDF files away. Well, I'm trying to anyway
Yeah, I do a lot of
go girl. I don't like. I thought we were talking about. I don't like those motherfuckers. If I can do anything I can to put them in jail, I will. Yeah. There you go. Yeah. Alex, Alex, I'm, I actually am a, I gave a listen to her and I actually used to join her and she, she does.
See that's
Would you ever would you ever let me like interview you officially summer because I would like
promote you and
Do what I can do because
That's amazing what I mean your life is amazing. I didn't know
That any of this about you and like now I'm just like wow
You
Well, I just you know, you get things get things you can go through things in life and you
and destroy you or you can come up out of it.
Wait, are you talking, wait, it's two to two.
He's literally, no, he's actually literally taught,
and he's not being a pervert.
He's actually talking about, he's the master debater.
And we just call him master debater.
I wanna clean that up real quick.
Cause I don't wanna put the clothes in a bag.
I was about to say, stop it, that's even crazy.
Some of you are here, you get.
I was about to go crazy. Yeah. Okay. No, it's we just call him a master debater. Okay.
He's the master debater. Okay. I was going to play on words. Play on words. I actually
No, I can see that
If you can see that
No, I didn't know because I'm not if I am punching your fuck it there. Let me see my punching your mouth
I did not allow you to punch me. I'm no and that's I don't even like
You know what? I don't like that analogy that analogy is
Mean you don't like that's cool. I understand that
That's all right. I can see you know, and I don't think I lost there. I just if I'm not on if I can't debate
I can't debate
Yeah, I'm sorry, I don't mean to
Debate for a second, but miss young young if you have something to say me you can bring your low-racist ass up on panel if you would like
Wait, who?
Have you have something to say to me? You don't have to say it in the chat. You can jump your ass up on this panel
I'm gonna get a piece of summer if you guys don't mind. Well, you can see that and I already what what no
Why do you want to whip my ass? I'm a girl. I don't want to know I don't want
Hey, psyche, you're really racist that friend in the chat needs to show the fuck out before she gets dragged
Yeah, I'm young the racist as fuck she's being racist as fuck see oh summer were you here last night?
I caught the
I've seen a little bit of it
Who is the racist let me know who's racist
I wanted I wanted a little piece of summer. I want a little piece of her
She goes by
Fuck all this shit
Not gonna back up. I don't I don't want to talk to anyone who's racist. I don't I don't want to deal
She ain't gonna come up here. She's not coming up here and why I'm up here. She knows I'll drag her ass. I don't deal with that
She's not coming up here
Yeah
Can we well like this is like he's
Channel like like
Yeah, that's why I brought attention
Wait, let's talk about
Because she's I mean Bob first not even in here and she's just starting up racist shit for no reason
And she's a model yours
And any who might be a job. Yeah, she's a lot of being anyone. He's being raised
It's like the end of that shit real quick. She's a mock
I'm trying to just moat a lot of weed and talk about psyche stuff. Really?
Yeah, but sometimes you have to address the least of so I can go away
Why is this person being racist how can we stop them we have to stop them who thank you
We can stop the racist if we figure out why they're upset
I've never been able to figure out why the racists are a summer was that handle or not
Yeah, I'd say handled
There's not a mod no more
Okay
All right, go ahead Alex. Well, I have a serious question. Why do you think the racist are the most upset?
How do we stop it?
That's a good question.
To me, I think racism is out of fear of what they don't understand, and so the fear turns
into hatred for no reason.
Half the time, people don't even know why they're racist.
It's a generational thing where they were taught that way.
Like I've been trying to, like-
I'm trying to tell everybody, my best friend is a gay fucking YouTube creator, I mean.
Like the racism I've experienced has been from people having stereotypes
But like stereotypes are changing
Okay, and how I don't think there's yeah, but that's less likely though
There's not really that much stereotypes. Like literally
I
The dude that you're you're on his family by the way, but my best friend and psyche
And I'm literally his best friend
Well, I don't think anyone on this panel is racist. Like, do you think I think you're racist?
I don't think
No, I know I well because we were because summer was talking about the racism because we were talking before about
What we were talking about we were talking about something and summer gave her and put on
I don't I don't know what we were talking about but we were talking about something but it was all relevant
But no, I bring it by the way. I'm just gonna point this out real quick
you were
Literally, we're we're talking about four foot ten gray. Oh, I'm just gonna point it out
Okay, well, I think it literally comes based out of a fear aspect something that I've experienced right because of like we as we know Alex right hate is not taught because when babies are born they look at you and they see you so
Innocently and they love you right you can hold a baby I can hold a baby they're gonna look at both of us the same exact way right because it's just
and my brother had my back, I don't give a fuck what color it was. We cured them this together.
Well, that's yeah, that's not right. That's you having your brother's back. That's not racism
Yeah, what me and Alex are talking about is there's people that are you know, because like okay
I come from a big family if somebody fought one of my sisters
Oh, baby, you would fight all of us, you know what I mean?
And that hadn't and we're a rainbow family all of us are different nationalities
So it had nothing to do with
And we're gonna go fight
As I was saying a second ago hold on hold on ghost one second sweetie
As I was saying a second ago babies when they're born
Racism to me is something out of and this is something that I've just experienced in my livelihood. I think it's fear
I think it's definitely taught. It's not something people are born with I think that a lot of people a lot of people that are racist
Either sometimes grow out of it when they get older because they're out of their parents household or whatever
But I really do think it's a fear-based thing. I do it is
But what I was going to say is that my personal experience with racism, I dealt with more racism when I was younger than now, like what's weird about being, and I noticed it, like, as soon as I hit around 40, for some reason, being like a middle-aged black woman.
There's nothing that like all of a sudden, like racism that you did deal with when you're younger. I don't know why this is me. I think I had to do the same thing.
Yeah, my husband says the same all of a sudden it was like it disappeared and I was like
Wow, but I do see it still with you
But it's not so bad with the youth like when I was young when I was young I
dealt with it more for like no reason than like a valid reason, but like
I don't know what maybe it's just the age that I'm at. It may be people view you in a different way
But well, you know, it's funny you say that Alex because when we moved out of Louisville where we live at now
I remember everybody was like, oh you guys are gonna move out there. It's so racist. You guys are interracial my husband's black
I'm I'm white passing, right? So okay, I would be like
So everybody's like, oh, you're gonna move out there and it's just racist. You guys need to be careful protect the babies
But blah blah blah, right? And I'm gonna tell you right now
First of all, we've not had not near one problem and second of all like these people are just love my husband's death
And I don't know what it is. Are you all around my age or are you? Yeah, we're around your age. Yes
My husband's like cuz you know, I fight racism in in my state because of their shit
But here what I'm where we live at. I don't do we don't deal with that
We've not had one issue now
I have had to go up to my daughter's school when we first got into town
Because my daughter's Hispanic very Hispanic passing and she's mixed, but she looks more Hispanic than anything
And so somebody told my daughter, you know, the first the first administration that went through when the whole Mexican and the wall and all that stuff
Was going on so my daughter go back to Mexico, right? My daughter was confused because she was like, well, what do you mean?
I was born here
I did I crashed out I went to the school and crashed the fuck out because I wanted them to understand that under no
Circumstances would I tolerate any of that and that was the one and only time and that was four years ago
So we've not dealt with anything out here ever since
So, you know, I'm really I like like
It's not for me to be sorry, but like I don't know not at all. I know what you're saying. Yeah
You understand you understand probably what my daughter felt, right? So, you know what I mean? Like my
well when when my mom and dad
Relocated it like I was born in Kirkland, Washington
And when I was a little girl in preschool, I was in Dallas playing out with my parents. My sister came along.
Then we moved to spring, which is outside of Houston.
It was a bit of a rough road like I don't know the details because I was a little girl
but I do remember
some things about my parents talking and
I even witnessed you know to where people did have to get used to seeing a
Little black girl. Yep. They had to get used to seeing a
Black couple with a little black girl or two little black girls
but I was the one who went into school first,
meaning like the elementary school,
and there were some other girls who were also
dark from India, like the East Indian area.
There was a couple of kids from like the East Asian area,
but because of a lot of the energy companies.
Bringing in people from other places. That's where the diversity came in
So we I mean we had to go to school. Oh, we were throw it in with a bunch of
Really Germanic people
We know it was crazy Alex like I grew up like you know in a very mixed household
You know, I mean the man that raised me is a black man. That's my daddy. Okay. No, but I got two fathers
I was my other and I have a daddy and I was blessed
I'm very lucky in that aspect right because I had two men that loved me enough to call me, you know
I'm their daughter
Yeah, 100% and so like when I got married both of them gave me away
That's how much I love my my father's right and it was
It was hard for me. I grew up with my granny. My granny marched with Martin Luther King, actually, way back in the day, right?
She lived in the North Carolina when this situation happened, Ari.
So why are you so excited to see her again this summer today?
Well, in Simpsons, yes, because I remember when I was little, I remember laying in my granny's living room,
and I remember a brick being thrown on the window, and it had the N-word on it, and I just didn't understand.
There was a cross that was burnt.
In the front yard scared to live and shit out of us like it was very very scary. It was very
As it's out
Here's my experience
I put my email in the back chat, um, if you want to grab that any time you want, you know, me that'd be great
Okay, I screenshot you can you can if you want to undo my screenshot it. Okay. It's all good. My emails stay out fun
But my experience is like a different one because I'll tell you what happened with me.
I never realized the difference growing because like I grew up in the environment.
Like looking back, I do see like, hey, people had to get used to seeing certain kinds of
people.
But growing up, I never experienced any racism until I was 12 years old.
That was the first time well, you know what was crazy is I and you know how you said Alex that you like you just didn't understand it
When I was little even though I was in a mixed household and stuff when people would be like all those stupid mixed kids
Or you know, whatever I didn't understand because I always thought this is how this is an innocent mind of a child
I just want to throw that out there first when I was little people would be like mix mix mix
And so I was like, well, what does the mix mean?
Does that mean one half of your body is black
and one half of your body is white?
Because for me, mixed families was so normal.
I didn't understand what the fuck they were saying to us.
You know what I mean?
I didn't understand what the problem was
that my daddy was black.
I didn't understand that the issue with my mom
was white Hispanic.
You know what I mean?
I didn't get it.
I just did not thought mixed kids would have your body
with white and have your body with black.
the first time. The whole time? Where's the mixed kids? I didn't even know what um racism or anything
was until I was about 12 and um oh that was when I that's when I started doing um you know I was
always like a like uh athletic kid I always did like a lot of sports and everything and I was on
the side. Yeah you look like you'd be athletic. Yeah and on the soccer team one day um it was
and there is a new kid, right, and the new kid was prejudiced.
and he looked at me and he's like,
has anyone ever called you a nigger before?
Just like that.
Oh, damn.
I, yeah.
Damn.
You just gonna say it?
I'm dead serious.
I didn't even know what it meant.
I never, I did not know.
And my friend, my best friend,
she knew what it meant and she got hit.
I didn't even, I really did not know.
And she got, she was about to fight the kid in the car.
So.
Because I didn't know what it meant like I was emotional. I was like wait wait
What is this me like am I bad like what is it just freaked me out? I didn't know what the fuck was going on. Okay, so
Her she but my friend told her mom her mom told my mom my mom
told the school and
It was this whole thing, okay?
It was a big thing because it was like no wait a minute no because it just
Hadn't happened
So it put me on the spot and it gave me a lot is the can I answer real can I buzz in real quick?
Can you please not say the word again?
I'm saying it in context and I'm a woman. I'm not saying it like but I'm not out to you know
You definitely didn't do it for like her. Yeah. Well, I just remember it. I'm
sending you're smoking. Look, I'm sending you're smoking some weed going through a
lot and we're talking about this. I hadn't thought about this in years. Yeah,
you and some were talking about my experience. That was my experience, but it
turned into this big thing and what it really came ended up coming down to was
that this particular family. Alex, you're going to show everyone the stars.
Wait what?
Yeah, they go ahead stars
Go ahead out
Well, it just turned into this thing to where it was very polarizing in our particular community and
My friends dad because my dad didn't my dad was going through a lot being
one of the few persons of color working for a corporation, okay?
So when this came about, that was kind of like,
well, my friend's dad was who basically told me,
you're going to have to kick that kid's ass.
And I'm just curious when I say this,
because this kid was trying to bully me.
I didn't even understand the level of bullying at that time,
but I'll tell you what did happen.
This might my friend. He was my friend's dad was like if you see this kid and he says this shit to you again
Punch him in the fucking face. He didn't say it like that, but he is like punch him in the face
And that's what I did. I did get suspended for three days. Well, listen, let me go. I'm proud of you
But you know what's weird summer I didn't even know the magnitude of that word and at that time of my life
That's what's crazy about it like you know
But your father knew the magnitude of that word and he taught you you know
I mean to stand up and and so you know it's I'm sure it's something you obviously have remembered your whole life because here
We are no it wasn't no it wasn't my dad. It was my best friend's dad. My dad couldn't do that
It was my it was my best friend.
Well, and then that makes it even better because somebody that completely understood what was
going on was like, yeah, no, we're not doing that.
You know what I mean?
So my first fight was with a boy.
I ain't gonna laugh.
Yeah, that was that was my first physical fight and he didn't hit me back either.
Yeah, my first fight I ever had was a boy.
Hold on one second. I was fighting them and I remember here and somebody say go get summer's dad
And next thing you know because we had a rule in my house like you you know, you're not gonna let nobody bully you
You're not gonna let anybody you know if you my message you fight him or you go home and and I'm gonna make you go back out
So I heard somebody say don't get go get her dad all of a sudden I ended up on top of this little boy and I was just crying and I was punching him in the face and I was like and I see my dad and I was like look I'm not I'm not losing my body.
Shomer.
No that's how it is.
Whenever you're keeping an eye for your cry.
Whenever you pick ass you cry.
God didn't want him to hit me.
I've been kicking men's asses since I was on top of that little boy crying my eyes out because I had to fight him.
But you showed you won.
I did win. I did win. No other little boy fucked with me for a long time.
I am disappointed in you.
Spank me.
Do you want to speak?
Wow, I got him to shut up for two seconds.
That was amazing.
Yeah, you want to be spanked?
Take a what?
Psyche. Psyche, you want to be spanked.
Oh, I'm sorry. Someone, sorry.
You're the one that should get spanked.
Psyche, do you want to be spanked?
Calm down. Calm down.
Fuck it, everyone can get a spank, Jared.
Calm down.
So, start with like, summer's the
next one, number two.
Well, I'm glad I came up here.
We got to actually talk a little
bit.
I came in your chat a couple
times.
Yeah.
Summer real quick, though,
before you.
I've been saying all night, I
actually do like Alex.
I actually do like her.
I like her a lot.
I actually really do.
She's logical.
Yeah.
Actually, I'm not logical
Yeah, you are a little bit. It's okay. Okay
Yeah, that's a good thing
We can we we can all be a hot
That was a good conversation like I thought I passed out man Sundays are always my long days
And I was out but I woke up and I seen you guys were laughing I was like well
I want to go tell go happy birthday little shithead and then I want to come up and you know
Maybe try to chat it up and obviously say how the page to
I didn't say happy birthday ghost and I said happy birthday
Appreciate it
Now you don't
Would you like me to sing happy birthday to you happy happy birthday happy happy birthday happy happy happy happy happy happy birthday
All right, there you go. Yeah
Happy birthday
Summer I went out open channel for my birthday. I don't want you to come up here like who I thought that was good
Well, wait, wait, wait. It's today your birthday or no, I am today. What it was
You know, I didn't get to see him though because I was asleep. You know, so
By the way, summer is a day late. I'm just
Well, I was like for three hours late
I feel like you're exploiting your birthday.
I am triggered.
You're exploiting your birthday.
I'm saying to crash out.
Yeah, you are crashing out.
You're exploiting and crashing out your birthday.
She said so much.
Oh, what's up everybody?
And that's that.
Chad, can we have another panel?
Who wants to open the panel?
I don't know Alex. I'll fucking chicken going she wants well
I was about to go to go to sleep. I'm like
Good night psyche good night summer
No, I'm not leading on a bad note. No, I had no thank you like me on the panel and being nice and everything
Thanks for being up here for my birthday. I really actually really appreciate it
Well, happy birthday and but it does seem like you're milking your birth because it's not technically your birthday anymore. Is it it only happens?
You know what? Maybe I don't want to go. Maybe maybe I want to pick on you.
You know what? She stays.
She stays.
Maybe I want to pick on you. How old are you? Fuck it. She Alex 32 which will be that she wrote 30 she stays
Fuck it. Let's run it. She stayed 30 30 32
Hmm. Do you do you think what have you accomplished in your 30? Alex? I don't I'm not interested in you
I'm not interested in some other
No, it's your birthday quiz
Okay, what about those?
It's the birthday. Well, what you don't want your birthday quiz
My birthday wish is with me.
You know, the quiz, Q-U-I-Z quiz.
It's time for your birthday quiz before I go.
Alright, go ahead.
You might not pass the quiz.
Really?
No, I'm not. No, it's
Universe I I I did I did a very brief
Don't brush me don't
Allen, I mean
Yeah, calm down
I'm trying to do the birthday quiz and he's like all like crazy
Well, yeah, that's a dub dub part. I mean, a little crazy. Do you mean the birthday quiz? If so, they're all. Well, do you want the birthday quiz or not? Yes, I really want one. Yes. Okay, it's going to be 10 questions. Are you ready?
I'm trying to think of some questions for you, okay, here's a good question.
What? I mean, did it touch on this before?
Ask the fucking question.
Well, I'm trying to.
What is the name?
Al, I mean, go, let her get it out.
Sorry.
Sorry
But matter of fact summer you fucking this is my work. You just call me Alex by the way
I'm talking about her on panel, but I'm not
I know what else you meant
I had to think of the question though trying to say the question. Yeah, she meant
Gee, I know Alex.
Well, everybody's Alex.
Now I don't talk to Alex, no more.
Alex, I'm Alex.
I talk to Alex, and they're out.
Is there another Alex?
There's a Nathan Alex,
and he's a hot fuckin' man.
Oh, I don't know about that, Alex.
Okay.
I'm a different Alex.
Oh, we're definitely a different Alex.
Okay.
Ask the fucking question.
Okay, here's the question.
What is the movie that Europa, that the moon Europa?
That would be Europa report.
That's the movie.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, there's an earlier, what 80s series of movie
Was there's no movie you're talking about more
Ropa's actually
You didn't let me really ask the question right? Oh my there's a there's a sci-fi
series
I don't even want a real quiz anymore
You're trolling you're you're you're just too intense how much for me
You're too intense for me right now, and I was trying you said you're the one that said Europe
No, I'm gonna ask you stupid questions now now now. I'm gonna ask you stupid questions. Okay. Um,
Who played Teen Wolf?
In the nice movie
Who played Teen Wolf in the 1980s?
So what's his what's his name? Can you name him? You got five seconds five four?
three
Two, I can send you when you fail. You're already on your way
No, you're down to 70% really cuz he didn't even let me ask question number two
So that was number three. Okay. Well, let's see how bad it gets. Okay. Let me try it. Let's help it
I'm trying to think of trivia. Well, at least summer's here. Well, it's too bad summer. Maybe summer wants to see you suffer
Because you're a little mean. Not summer. It's me
Well, maybe hate wants to see you suffer too. You're a little mean. It's locked out. It's me. We like a little suffering. It's kind of fun
We're like a little hot mess back. I like a little pig myself. Here's here's another question for you
Okay, so I'm gonna try to ask something age-appropriate to you. That's it
Let me think about it. Let me think about
I do appreciate you going to let us have a conversation a little bit.
I, I, I, I, you know what? I don't have any questions.
Happy birthday to you.
I don't have any more trivia questions. I'm too tired.
What the fuck are you talking about? Oh, I'm not even going to crash out. That was
retard. I'm crashing out. I have all these questions. I got five questions you have to do.
I did ask you. I asked you three questions. Come on, Alex. Come on. Alex, come on.
I'm too tired because I don't, I don't, I don't really know your age range. Alex.
You're in your thirties. Thirty-two. That's my age range. Come on, Alex. Come on.
Yeah, go ahead and ask it.
Yeah, I'm so sorry about these.
OK, no, here's a question for you.
What was the name of the Fresh Prince of Bel Air's cousin,
his male cousin?
What was his name?
Carlton.
Okay, that's good. You know that don't know. Can you ask me when I'm finna crash out?
I am finna crash out. This is my birthday by the way. This reminder. I'm finna crash out.
Well, don't don't crash out bad
In a good way crash out in a good way. You don't want me to do now.
No, you can make fun of me like you can pick on me. It's just your birthday
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I I should ask her I should ask a summer question. Okay. Do you want do you want it? Well, fuck it
Well, what do you want it's your birthday? Yeah, I'm trying to fucking ask fucking ask her
Okay
Oh, okay. Who was the... I have a question for Summer. She'll know the answer, but she'll have to think about it.
What was the name of the villainess on Melrose Place?
Oh, um...
Was it the brown hair? She was always seen as the villain. Wouldn't she or or the dude um
The fuck with the brown hair. No, no the blonde the villain is she was like the bad girl on
Melrose place. Oh, okay
I thought it was always Shannon Dory because she always played the like the bad girl. No. No, that was 90210. Oh
My bad wrong show, but she was kind of a good girl
I did walk to my old place too, I just, yeah, I can't remember all their names.
It was Amanda, Amanda, Heather Locklear's character.
Oh, yes, okay, yeah.
Yeah, I used to watch that. I think my girlfriend wouldn't be listening to that show on three way back in the day when three way was existing.
Oh my god, I remember that. I remember
She's on the phone with all your friends three way watching the show together.
I remember plugging in a super long foam cord into my mom's bedroom.
So I had a phone in my room with it like a splitter so I could talk to my friends on the phone
Oh my in high school, right?
Yeah, it's crazy and your brothers could listen in and make them
Well, I didn't have any yeah, I just had a nosy little sister. That's it. Well, yeah
Yeah, I had brothers and they would pick up the phone and say random stupid shit. I feel like come on
Do you remember the party lines?
Yes, I remember the party lines. Yep
Man
Well, this is this is a summer Alex
But oh I got a question for you, okay
Yeah, for you for you. It's a birthday question. Okay. Oh
I'm gonna take you back to the 80s
Okay
What was well too bad you you have to be smart, okay
What was the county?
That Bill and Ted's excellent adventure took place in
What County of California?
Make up your mind give me a definitive answer
You said it
Let us assume you're asking questions. Let me
You're not confident your answer I heard you say you said see I'm barundi though
You know I have a question ask you Alex on some road shit though real quick. This is my birthday real quick or
Are you a male or female?
I'm a female. Yeah
I
Know you know what asshole, I'm one of the few people who has public
When I was younger I was in the porn industry so you can actually view my genitalia
Setting if you decide to do so to so you can verify that I'm biological
You talk
You're hurry wait you want to hear about it
All right, here we go fucking annoying. I'm gonna hurt about it now. I'm so fucking
Alex, happy birthday. Happy, happy birthday. Well, summer's supposed to be my friend or something.
Don't know what that means. He is your friend. I'm still telling you. No, no, no. I won't.
I mean, we can do a live on our own here if you want. We'll come on with me, but I just woke up.
I don't know what to tell you, sweetie. Summer, I'm hurt. Tell your husband I'm fucking hurt right now.
He's just my husband. I actually saw it. I'm actually really hurting. I'm not gonna lie to you. I'm actually really hurt
You're really hurt. No, you're not really hurt. I'm hurt and I'm hurt
Whatever
How am I not hurt go ahead? I'm fucking sure summer's my friend well, she was
Talking
You sound like you're smiling as you're talking
I just woke up
I should have been ghost open panel. Have your birthday ghost. That's what I should be doing.
Well, baby, I'm sorry, but I was asleep. I was working since nine o'clock this morning.
No, you don't get to control your own, but you get to control your birthday party. That's for
other people. Like I gave, uh, like I control, uh, so I didn't like, you get to control your
What would you like me back here?
I don't think your birthday is your birthday week.
So we could do a birthday panel anytime this week.
He wants to get his own birthday party.
I don't think that he gets to control your own birthday party.
Happy birthday ghost open panel.
Surprise party.
No, he wants too much control over his birthday party.
I'm just saying, don't ask me what I want from the birthday ones.
That's what I want.
Well, it's still early, so we have your birthday week.
We can, you know, I got to work this morning too.
Don't take my opinion into account.
I have no opinion. I, I, I, my opinion is should not be admissible into this court of public opinion.
If I can't even argue wasting some of the fuck off, which I've done, I've literally got to go.
I don't want, I don't want my opinion to be admissible into this court of public opinion. No.
It shouldn't be admissible.
It shouldn't be. No, I'll admit it. I don't, I definitely...
No, why do you not take it there? Stop taking it into words and to other realms. Stop that. Leave me alone.
You know what? What's your last name? Is that made clear?
Well, it's publicly known. Mayors. Mayors.
That's Sir.
So my thought about it, I'm finna crash out
Are you crashing out?
Or am I crashing out?
You're crashing it out. I'm crashing!
I crashed.
Past MC crashed out.
Yeah, I crashed.
You crashed out from my heart, kid?
I'm just saying that I crashed out.
I think he's sleeping, I think he's sleeping, I think he's asleep, I think he went to bed.
How long have you guys been live?
Um, it says four hours and 31 minutes.
Oh damn, there's a clock right there.
Yeah, I'm glad you went live tonight.
Yeah, I mean I was I was looking for a panel just to you know vibe and you know be on
So I came on here, and I think it was a cool conversation
I mean, I don't care if it's an argument. That's that's what makes us spicy and fun
So yeah, well, can I give a little bit of a push back?
A little bit of what?
Fresh back you're gonna give me a voice
Wait, I couldn't hear you wait. What do you say? Hi, what'd you say guys?
I don't have the power to pick you
That is true. I
I don't I can't I don't have the
Ability
I didn't kick you.
I wish I was the all-powerful kicker.
Thank you very much.
If I was an all-powerful kicker
of all the panels in existence.
All-powerful kicker of that?
Could you imagine?
I would just like, just for fun,
I would just like wake up in the morning.
Go on to any panel. I saw I'm just tricking people. I sure would
Yeah, they accused me of the same thing to say like oh you brought his panel. Well the fucker if I ran it
Let me run it
Yeah
They're they're like if I had like superpowers, I would do odd things
Now we're everyone
What are we doing
We're going to your channel and it's gonna be a special open panel. Happy birthday goes
Oh
My husband's clothes smells good
Why your husband will fucking join the panel he has to hang out with her husband. She doesn't have time for your birthday
No, I just sent him to work
Tugles that is a fair argument. Welcome up couples
Yeah, he just left for me.
I don't know about you ghost. I feel like you're trying to do something that you shouldn't be doing. I don't know about you
I mean, that's a fair fucking argument. Let's go ahead and explain what am I trying to do.
Well, I think you know what you're doing, but I'm observing, but I just think you need to slow your roll.
You need to slow your roll.
Summer is slow.
She's no, you need to slow your roll. Not summer. You. You need to say your role. Listen. Listen. Well, I'm listening. All right. I am. You're sorry. I like. You're being there. I'm not. No, slow down.
Don't call me good. Don't call me. Well, that's what you're supposed to well. Yeah, listen your name crash out gifts
Crush it down. I'm gonna crash out. I'm not even alive
Yeah
Yeah, well
Well, I got a good bite. I got I got a lead down
That's a little jerry
Well, I crashed out I think I'm like the crash out
Crash outer of the crash out. Well, that's it. I know you're afraid if someone does open that panel up, you know, it's gonna happen, right?
That's not psyching statement
Well, I thought I was going to wake up. Are you gonna wake psyche? Are you sleep?
Are you asleep psyche? Yeah, I sleep
All right, well summer it was really really just like cool connecting with you and I'm sorry that I had to put up with mr. Crash out over here
You know
I really like talking
Yeah, yeah, most likely well, we'll do this again. Well ghost you're you are the crash out came
Alex do you still believe in aliens that are four-foot? Yes, I do. I do and they're great, right?
Yeah
Yeah, yeah
But I hope you have a happy birthday
I hope I was very happy
Well, do you well do you have a birthday wish that you got that you made?
Oh, I my birthday wish would be for a summer to open a fucking channel
you're more than welcome to come. Don't be manipulative. Oh sorry. Even though it's your birthday. Don't
ask me what my fucking wish is then. Okay all right well I'm not gonna do anything. What do you want?
Then I say what I want and you say don't do that. I know. I know. Well that's what women do,
that's what I do. I'm sorry. And by the way can I ask you real quickly real quick?
Why do you sound like a woman like the whole time?
Now you kind of sound like a man.
Because she's a woman.
I'm tired now.
I mean, I'm not a man.
No, I'll turn on my camera.
Alright, the more tired I am, the more like a man.
Wait, no.
No, I'll turn my freaking, let me go into the light.
I'm a woman.
I'm not a man.
Hold on.
I'm a woman. I mean, I think
I'm a woman. I'm a woman.
Do you know what? I want you to
the bed before the four foot
because I don't want to have
any nightmares. I'm off to bed
and I'm susceptible to
Okay, I'm not a man. Well, why do you suddenly sound like a woman? It's ma'am. It's ma'am
You sound you sound like a woman
Why
She's a gorgeous woman. I
I am I am I am I am I am an alien. I'm a little alien
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What role I'm not even three feet tall
I'm an Elton
Happy birthday, okay, I gotta go happy birthday
Have a good birthday. I might open up for a little bit. I hope all your wishes and
Dreams that you deserve come true. You don't deserve them. I hope they don't come true
But if they if you do deserve them, that's what they do
Well, I don't know because maybe you don't deserve something, but maybe you do deserve other things
That's my
Happy birthday. Thank you.
That's really magical to me. That was really good. That was really good.
Upon you. Really good night. Yeah. Good night.
Good. Happy birthday. Have a good night, Summer.
Bye bye. All right, Sweet. Have a good night.
I might open up for like an hour. That's about it.
Good night, Psychi. You know what?
What
You know, I guess I hope that an alien abducts you for your birthday
Well, I'm going to make sure that they beam you up into a force field.
Are you going to beam me up, ma'am?
You can never, yeah.
Are you going to make sure that I'm going to do it? Go ahead.
I am. I'm going to call my alien.
You realize, you realize, you're an artist. You don't know what the fuck you were talking about.
Fuck you.
I do know what I'm talking about.
I'm gonna call the aliens and they're gonna beam you up
Yeah, you better not go to sleep. Don't shut your eyes
All right, happy birthday
All right, I might open up for about an hour hour or so
Just kidding. Let's open it up. It's my birthday
All right, well if a mod wants to drop the link to talk here, I'm gonna go set it up for a little bit since like you're sleeping
Yeah, I'll be back. I won't be back. I'll see you guys over there
All right
You